<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Coyotes in Space - blog/2019</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://coyotesin.space/feeds/blog/2019.atom.xml" rel="self"/><id>https://coyotesin.space/</id><updated>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</updated><entry><title>Camping dreams are weird</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-05-23:/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around for stuff on the trail, but as it got later, I ended up stopping for the night at a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good friend of mine who's big in pooltoys said "Yeah man, you can't beat the classics" in a voice I absolutely know I've heard him use IRL, but he was using it about a backpack that converted into a cot instead of a toy. I dunno why he was there, pfft. But it was still neat! Talked briefly to folks before going to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next morning my parents were somehow involved, and I was getting ready to pack up for the day, but apparently not hiking out yet, cause my sister and brother-in-law said something about messing up something on my car. Don't know why it was there. But then they were confused that we weren't yet leaving for the trail and would be spending the day in-town. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the day, I left to go buy supplies, but ended up buying lotto tickets. Turned around after buying them, and started wandering, only to find what looked like an entrance to a spacious Artist's Alley in a furry convention, and peeking in, I found a good friend of mine. Wandered over and said hey, and got a big warm hug, and I remember it making me super happy to see him, hee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird, but fun dream! I'd love more happy camping/backpacking/hiking dreams!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="camping"/><category term="dreams"/><category term="cons"/></entry><entry><title>Fursona Sundries</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-04-19T07:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-19T22:39:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-04-19:/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play around with formatting a great deal but, hope folks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I'd like help with is a good way to format the miscellaneous information this page has!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/sundry.html"&gt;Check out the page here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class="accordions"&gt;
  &lt;article class="accordion"&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-header toggle"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Also playing with spoilers...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-body"&gt;
      &lt;div class="accordion-content"&gt;
        I've added a new bulma extension, for accordion support. Gonna use for spoilers. So much for no javascript, but CSS-based ones are a bit funky, maybe. We'll see!
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you can embed HTML in Markdown articles in pelican and it'll play nice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="furry"/><category term="writing"/></entry><entry><title>Returning to the guitar?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-01-27:/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved how the guitar sounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I've been thinking about it again. I'd first thought of snagging an electric guitar to learn on, but now I'm not certain I want to go that route. I miss the tone of an acoustic guitar, and I want to go that route. I decided to ask a friend who has been working on guitars for decades about it, and he's helping me out with picking out a starter, and encouraging it. And that's really helpful for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds silly I'm sure, but a part of this kinda inspired a comic idea, too, with Kay. But there's a little background and character detail I want to go over as well, to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay is really my fursona anymore. I'm silly and bouncy like he is, and get very giddy and giggly. But despite his toony, toyish nature, he's not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a toy. I think of 'toy' as more like an additional feature of him, not something that reduces or subtracts from him being a coyote. And I feel like that's kinda different as far as squeaksonas go. He has a normal job (like me), goes hiking and backpacking (like me), and loves music (like me). He can be happy and bouncy, or sad and morose, depressed even. Being a toy-type doesn't remove that at all. So that puts art involving him in an interesting place, trying to figure out or help an artist figure out in future ideas juxtaposing his slightly toony nature with perhaps more-serious situations. Which brings me to the comic idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: this goes into depression territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay, after his permanent transformation into a toy, possibly 'courtesy' of Coyote or some other deious entity, is a tremendous waterfall of feelings. Whilst he's always adored balloons and inflatables, being one, despite the excitement of it, is also terrifying. Though he's immune to most concerns of puncture and the like, there's the fears about being taken seriously anymore, about what others will think of him, about how he'll keep going in school and studies, and jobs later. Of what his parents would think. Even if he enjoys the form, he hates it (at first) as well. This has a huge toll on his psyche for canonically several days, maybe weeks. Even if he's enjoyed some inflationy fun with close friends, it still doesn't take his mind, ultimately, off of the "problem". &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going home the night after his TF, it's dark in his dorm when he arrives, wandering in with the lights off, and slumping onto his bed. He catches sight of his guitar and, after a moment of adjusting, finds he can still play, this wasn't taken from him. Playing slowly helps give him a little bit of a boost, to make him feel at least a little more like it's alright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damn. Writing it out like that... Maybe this doesn't need a comic. ~~Maybe this needs a short story, and a picture to go with it. Wonder what I can do in a thousand words. Doesn't seem like enough.~~ So I ended up writing out a short story of 1000 words, including articles, for it. May go back and update it to be 1000 words without articles, just to help it stand on its own better. &lt;a href="/files/Strings.pdf"&gt;It's right here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anywho, just a musing thinking about it. I'm excited to get back into this. I want to hear that sound again from my own fingers. I'm starting to take a bit of flight of my own in many ways, and this is just one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="music"/><category term="learning"/><category term="hobby"/><category term="writing"/></entry></feed>