<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Coyotes in Space</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://coyotesin.space/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://coyotesin.space/</id><updated>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Recovery</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/recovery.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-03-07:/articles/2024/recovery.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welp, sickness sucks. Emergencies suck more. Strap in, this one's definitely got some fun. 
Content Warnings: surgery, pain, medical, gross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So! Sunday evening, the 3rd, I started to feel a little bit of what I thought was just gas pain. I normally get it in my middle of my abdomen …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welp, sickness sucks. Emergencies suck more. Strap in, this one's definitely got some fun. 
Content Warnings: surgery, pain, medical, gross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So! Sunday evening, the 3rd, I started to feel a little bit of what I thought was just gas pain. I normally get it in my middle of my abdomen, and it sucks, but it goes away eventually. This did not. It persisted, slowly getting worse. I kept farting here and there hoping that was relieving it, but it never truly did. I struggled with the bathroom, but it kept getting more persistent. It eventually started to spread outward, encompassing my lower right in it. By this point, it was probably 11 PM or later? I thought it might be appendicitis, but in that "WHAT IF IT WAS CANCER???" kind of way. Thank WebMD for fears like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pain persisted and I kept trying to sleep, whimpering, tossing and turning as I kept shifting in the hopes it'd go away. Certain types of abdominal pressure helped, but overall it was just bad constantly. I finally fell asleep once I took Tylenol, which helped the pain subside some.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come Monday morning, I felt better, no more weird gas pain, but something else was there -- this weird nagging 'persistent' feeling in my left side. There was a presence there that insisted I know it was there, like using a highlighter on a word on white paper, but this was internal. I couldn't get rid of the nagging sensation. Nothing helped, and as the day wore on, lack of sleep kept me tired but feeling bad overall. Something was clearly wrong. I was talking to Mathias about it, who had asked about specifics the night before and wanted to keep an eye on specific feelings. He finally came over early afternoon to stay with me and help me feel better, but the sensation wouldn't go away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With both of us hoping it was something benign ultimately, some new sensation with IBS, we went to an urgent care clinic to check it out. There, they couldn't do much, a urinalysis, but overall nothing. But then the nurse practitioner came in, spoke to me, poked a little, and said I was presenting a lot of the classic signs of appendicitis -- pain and tenderness in the lower right, pressure, nausea, rebound pain when pushing on the left side of me, lower GI issues beyond IBS. It was probably serious, so she told me to go to an emergency department (ED/ER) and tell them the urgent clinic sent me with concerns of appendicitis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walf and I were still hoping that the imaging would rule it out -- I had no fever, no vomiting, no intense pain like people described with it being the worst pain they'd ever felt. But a CT scan showed the attending nurse practitioner (NP) at the ED that I almost certainly had acute appendicitis, and an hour later radiology concurred. The main hospital would set me up a room, and I would ride in an ambulance for the first, and hopefully last, time. (BUMPY!) I was told I'd almost certainly be operated on by a surgeon the NP had perform on him once, which was a pretty glowing review to me! I was also comforted by hearing that it'd also likely be laparoscopic, minimally-invasive -- just 3-4 little tiny incisions on the belly to operate and that's it! (Spoiler alert: this did not happen.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They couldn't schedule me for surgery that night, so they transported me to the main hospital, and up to my room there, allowing Mathias to spend the night there with me and helping him get some bedding in the room with me. I was in pain, but treated with morphine that helped the pain considerably at low dosage, only 2mg at a time -- 4mg gave this TERRIBLE rush sensation up the back of my shoulders and neck that I &lt;strong&gt;hated&lt;/strong&gt; feeling. I don't get why people like it. But the low dosage helped, and I slept, intermittently because of repeated waking, but I still slept.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a side note, the nurse at this time, at the hospital, had some indirect connections, apparently having worked at the same Panera a good local friend of ours works at, and her fiance having worked for the same computer repair place I worked at after I left it. Small world! She was SUPER nice and helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waking, I met that doctor I was told about, who told me he'd be making sure he could do the minimally-invasive and then I'd be feeling better soon. Much more pain today, but again, managed through drugs. But soon after, I met a different doctor, who said &lt;em&gt;he'd&lt;/em&gt; be doing my surgery instead, and that he would &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; do the laparoscopic -- not because he didn't know how or wasn't good at it, but because he didn't "like" it. "But then you have 3-4 incisions and scars instead of just one!" I think I'd have preferred that over what I have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever. He reassured both Mathias and I and so I was promptly prepped for surgery, taken down to pre-op, where the din of the place and the sounds, the treatment, the disorganization (four &lt;strong&gt;different&lt;/strong&gt; people asked me the same questions!) had me quickly skyrocketing in anxiety, and Mathias thankfully was back there and with me because I broke into tears at some point. He also gave me my earplugs, but well before I was given the drug to start to go under general anesthesia, a nurse told me I had to take them out, which sucked because they were helping me manage my anxiety. I was scared, and upset, but the lady shaving my belly for surgery helped me calm a fair bit. Pain, but she was comforting with talking a little as she did, and taking her time. At some point I was given a large dose of ondansetron for upcoming nausea and then an anti-anxiety drug that had me calming down, everything feeling melty, and promptly passing out without even realizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next thing I knew, just like with tooth surgery, I was in considerable pain and they were trying to help with things in post-op, getting stuff worked out, talking about room transfers as if I'd end up in a different room than I'd been in. But finally they decided the same room I'd been in, and I was transported -- feeling every. Fucking. Bump. The most minor bumps, the acceleration of a rotation even gentle, starting or stopping and ESPECIALLY those GOD DAMN ELEVATOR BUMPS felt like HELL on where I'd been operated on. I could barely move, I was trying not to cry, just tired and stressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then they picked me up, sheet and all, and put me in my bed again. And my pain spiked so high I yelped as it shot up past a 10 for me there, and I promptly broke down sobbing as they left -- feeling tired, afraid, hurting, abandoned by them, cared &lt;em&gt;at&lt;/em&gt; instead of &lt;em&gt;for&lt;/em&gt; and just... terrible. Upset and angry my want for laparoscopic had been overturned because some old doctor didn't "like" it. Who fucking cares if it takes longer, I'm unconcious, what the shit do I care? It felt like he was just trying to speedrun surgery instead of &lt;strong&gt;patient&lt;/strong&gt; care being the focus, and just reminded me so much of how many people feel this way in the US's current medical treatment pipeline. I just wanted everything to feel better -- even remembering now I'm choking a little because of how bad it felt. But Mathias was there for me, and held my hand and what he could safely do of me and kissed my head, staying close as I cried with the pain and hurt of it. I had no option here, I had to get surgery immediately or I would've died, I had no chance to pick a doctor or facility, I was stuck with whatever I had. Every jingoistic asshole talking about how "Americans have choice in healthcare though" compared to other systems can fuck RIGHT the hell off, they've clearly never had emergency care needs because I don't get to fucking pick, I just have to hope wherever I end up is covered by my insurance or that I can fight with my insurance for it. I'm grateful that my insurance will likely make this expensive, but still something I can afford, though I don't feel like it's right for me to have to pay $800-1000 just because some part of my body decided to fuck up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pain meds helped, and some water, some rest, and I started to feel a little better. I felt well enough to eat the dinner I was served in full, and in full I did -- I was starving at this point, Tuesday evening, since I'd had nothing to eat since Monday early afternoon. I rested in and out a fair bit, woken repeatedly for vitals and the like. I had to repeatedly watch for air in the line because people were inattentive too, I pointed out a large one to a nurse in training just before she injected some into me, and had to withdraw it which pulled blood into the IV line, oh well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Wednesday morning I just wanted to go. I wanted things over. I wanted pain to stop, I wanted everything normal, but I couldn't. My gut was starting to try to move again, but couldn't, and as I was getting released, I started to get gas pain again, but this time it was very clearly just gas pain moving around the small intestines and into the large one. But finally I was discharged after the nurse's attitude changed some I think seeing how stressed and upset I was from everything. There seemed to be constant miscommunication, or misunderstanding, and the nurse pointed out that's all it was but...that doesn't change how I as a patient feel in that situation. It sucked. Again, I felt cared &lt;em&gt;at&lt;/em&gt; rather chan cared &lt;em&gt;for&lt;/em&gt; and I couldn't really word it any other way. The act of caring without directly caring for me individually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, I worked through it, nurse helped me with walking some more, good advice, and I was given medication to drop my blood pressure from being so high and then released. Also at this point I had a LOT of gas discomfort and bubbling and I was trying badly to fart, so bad that the first time I did I almost moaned with relief. It felt like the best fart ever because holy hell, you don't realize what it feels like when that whole system just STOPS and then needs to start again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing this while at my desk, while Mathias is in the living room working at my work desk, staying with me. Immensely grateful for him being here. I told my boss I'll be out this week and be back WFH on Monday, though may be WFH that week. I'll recover. It'll take some time, but I'll be back to normal again soon I hope.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2024"></category><category term="hospital"></category><category term="surgery"></category><category term="pain"></category></entry><entry><title>Stranded</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/stranded.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:59:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:59:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/stranded.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cody, a coyote in his late 20s, has been abandoned at a truck stop with nowhere to go, and the manager won't permit him to sleep in the chairs instead of a bunk. And all of those are taken.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Sir?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody grunted softly, stirred from a doze. He blinked several times, looking around blearily, realizing he’d dozed off. He took in his surroundings, seated in a sitting area near the food court of the truck stop. Looking out the large pane window before him, the same site he’d seen a few hours ago greeted him: a black night sky and a furious blizzard’s clumps and flakes billowing past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sir? I’m sorry, sir, but you can’t sleep here,” came the voice again, belonging to a small ferret, a clerk, the coyote surmised, based on the name tag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinking away the remaining daze, he simply nodded. “Yeah uhm… sorry. I didn’t mean to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret smiled, chuckling. “I can tell. Here,” he replied as held up one of the stop’s paper mugs towards the sleepy canine. “My manager won’t try to get me to kick you out as long as you’re awake. I’m sorry we don’t have any spare bunks right now, with the blizzard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote nodded, a weak smile flashed in return. The ferret was cute, he thought to himself, as he quietly accepted the mug, taking a long sip. “Thank you,” he replied softly. He held the mug close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the TV mounted high behind the ferret blinked, the coyote’s eyes quickly snapped to it, drawn by the change, realizing it was a weather screen. The gaze caught the ferret’s attention as well, who turned to look up at the forecast, and back to Cody with a grim expression. “Looks like we’re both gonna be stuck here for a while… listen, uh,” the ferret turned back to the coyote, pausing a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote chuckled. “Cody...my name’s Cody.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling, the ferret nodded. “Thomas. Listen, Cody, if uh...your...friends...don’t arrive for you soon…” he started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s expression fell slightly, his ears leaning back. “It’s that obvious?” The tone, the phrasing and pauses, all told a story that the ferret knew the reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas’ expression fell as well. “Only to someone like me. But, uh,” he quieted his voice to just over a whisper, for only the canine’s ears. “If a room doesn’t clear up, and you don’t find someone to hitch a ride with, within the next 3 hours, I’ll meet you by the employee door down the shower hall. My employee bunk’s big enough for both of us short skinny guys.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody paused a moment after listening. “Tom…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret put a finger to the coyote’s muzzle, hushing him gently, before speaking again with a lowered voice. “You’re cute, and I’ve seen you here twice before in the past couple months, and based on who you left with and showed up with, I can tell what happened, and I don’t want you hurt or worse,” he whispered, before grinning up at the coyote more goofily. “And it’s ‘Thomas’, not ‘Tom’… gay guys don’t go by short names.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote burst out in an intense laugh, far stronger than he expected to at the response and struggling not to spill his gifted coffee. “Ahaha, I...thank you, Thomas, I...I needed that. And...thank you,” he replied as he calmed back down, a softer expression having replaced the more forlorn one he wore before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas smiled, turning to head back towards the counter. “Don’t thank me yet, it’s only for a night, and I don’t put out,” he replied as he padded towards the register he’d been working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody turned back to face the window and the storm, as he leaned onto his knees, the warm aroma of the coffee drifting to his nose. “After what brought me here...me neither,” he whispered to the concoction, whilst staring into the swirling snowscape outside as if it held answers he was desperate to divine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a lot cleaner than the normal bunks,” Cody murmured as the door closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret quietly giggled, reaching over to click on a switch, illuminating a rope light tethered to the wall in an organic squiggle. “Well yeah, each employee gets their own little room like this. Now don’t be too loud, there’s nothing saying I can’t do this, but I don’t want to test things,” he said, reaching behind the coyote to lock the door to the ferret’s tiny, private bunk room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I would’ve figured they’d have y’all sharing stacked bunks, this is kinda nice,” Cody added, more quietly. Casting his glances around, he found a small nook under the folding desk to drop his backpack, before turning to the ferret, who’d already shimmied out of his company smock and hung it on a peg on the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, this place was built before they started doing that at the other locations. Both of our luck,” Thomas replied as he poked the coyote’s middle gently. “I won’t push you to take off any more than you want, don’t worry. The only payment I want is to snuggle up with a cute guy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody chuckled, but smiled warmly at the response. “Well at least someone is into me for more than just sexual favors,” he mused, as he started tugging his thick hoodie and shirt up over his head, his ears flicking as the hems cleared them, his gray, tawny, and brown fur slightly matted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas was down to just boxers by the time the coyote slipped the top garments off, and wore a soft frown. “That bad?” he asked, softly, with a tone of concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After starting to undo his jeans, Cody paused, and then sat on the small bed beside Thomas. “Yeah. I...I should’ve seen it coming. I moved clear across the country for that asshole and he got pissed just cause I wouldn’t fuck his friends or do drugs with them, and told me I was too ‘weird’ with...my..uhm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret poked at the coyote’s barely-covered waist, trying not to outright grope him. “With making the house smell like latex or balloons?” Thomas asked with a bit of a grin, gently pinching the waistband of the black latex boxer briefs the coyote’d stopped undressing to hide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s cheeks tinged pink for a moment, but he nodded, slipping those jeans off entirely to let the glossy garment shine in the dim light. “Both. You’re uh...you’re good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas laughed softly, then bent over for a small bag on the floor. After retrieving something, he stripped his boxers off entirely, not making any attempt to hide his cute butt from the coyote, until he stepped into the garment he’d fetched and slid it up. And as he sat back beside Cody, their hips squeaked lightly, the ferret changed into a matching pair of latex shorts, though purple. “Comes with familiarity, I guess. Now get under the covers here; I’ve always wanted to snuggle up wearing these with a guy who also is, and it’s fucking cold, you damn canines have no concept of indoor temps with that warmer coat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote paused, taken by significant surprise, and blushing a little more as he shifted to the back of the cot to let Thomas slide in in front of him, and drew the blankets up over the pair. He wrapped an arm around Thomas’ side, gentle at first, and then relaxing as he settled into the contact, quietly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few moments of the quiet affection, with hips lightly squeaking with their gentle movements, the ferret turned to face Cody, and pressed his face into that warm, fluffy chest. “Hope we both can find who we’re looking for,” he spoke softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cause you don’t have room or money to take me in; I wasn’t even thinking of asking, don’t worry,” Cody replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, you silly dog, because we’re both such bottoms we’d drive each other nuts!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote had to tuck his snout into the pillow to muffle his laughter. Clocked, teased, and it all true. “Fuck, you’re right, snrk… But this?” he asked, emphasizing his intent as he stroked his claws softly through the ferret’s fur along his back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas squirmed and wiggled in true noodle fashion with a chitter, followed by a giggle. “This? Cuddling a cutie like you? I’m hoping I get to again some night,” he replied sweetly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote rested a paw on the ferret’s rubbery-coated flank, gently squeezing, clearly more to explore the material than outright grope his new friend. “Me too.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Sleeper</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/sleeper.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:58:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:58:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/sleeper.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After a cozy night with the charitable clerk stuck snowed-in as well, Cody needs some form of rescue, and finds it in an unlikely being: a timberwolf named Brandon, made entirely of rubber and air.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cody tried not to keep staring at the ferret as he worked. A second night was promised if he absolutely had to, but with the clerk’s shift only starting 2 hours ago, the coyote wasn’t sure he could keep awake that long. He continued staring out the window into the blizzard. The same sight as the night before, hardly changed. Even during the day, it hardly seemed to get light out, between the latitude and blizzard raging outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody stood for a moment, and took a sip of the coffee Thomas gave him a few minutes prior. A nice perk, and he’d seen the ferret let a few kinder folks with refill mugs leave if all they got was coffee. “Why bother?” he’d told the coyote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He walked over to the door, taking a step out into the blustery cold. The fur of his nap bristled and fluffed, but he only felt the cold seep in after a moment standing there. “To think my ancestors probably just curled up in the snow in weather like this,” Cody mused with a dry chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thoughts swirled in his mind as he looked towards the black clouds above. Abandoned. Ejected. Hated. He looked down into his coffee, as if for something else. No words came.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘Selfish.’ ‘After all he did for you.’&lt;/em&gt; The coyote practically stumbled back, leaning against the wall. “Stop it…” he whispered to the empty lot before him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What made you think this would be different? What made you think this would work out?’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because I loved him,” the coyote choked, his throat tight. “Stop…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘You loved the idea of him. You loved the idea of being cared about, of being important to someone, why would—’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I SAID FUCKING STOP!” Cody shouted, as salty ice formed below his eyes. “Fucking fuck off!” His voice didn’t even echo in the snow, as the thoughts quieted, leaving him panting, and shaking. “Fuck,” he said, much more quietly, wiping his face on his coat with a sniff before turning back inside. Away from the cold. Away from even colder thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Cody stepped back inside and wiped his shoes on the carpet, splaying his toes to get the snow out from under them as well, he caught a whiff of a new scent. Or not so much new as new-in-context. He returned to his backpack, sniffing around it briefly, and then down at himself. Nothing. Maybe Thomas took a cue from him to ‘stealth’ today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody shrugged it off, settling back down to sit again, and look out into the snow, letting the din of truckers coming and going roll past as he focused on the falling flakes, as they danced and wheeled about. “Maybe I could just get a job here?” he mused to himself. It was peaceful enough. The truckers had been friendly. It was a nice change from what he’d seen where he grew up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“...Cody…”, Thomas said, perking up the coyote’s ears. As they swiveled for a fix, the bustle settled into a few distinct voices. He couldn’t clearly focus on the ferret anymore, but he knew he’d heard his name amongst the various sounds, a few new ones blending into the mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before turning his head to see what the ferret was up to, the scent of rubber graced his nose once more. And in caution again, he sniffed at himself, downward, then towards his backpack. Nothing. Only a faint hit, not the warmer one. Not the strength he picked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, you Cody?” spoke an unfamiliar voice, and as the coyote turned his head to his addresser, his eyes widened. The question of the scent was immediately answered. The timberwolf before Cody stood easily half-again the coyote’s height, if not more, a trucker given the vague stereotype of a white t-shirt covered by an unbuttoned plaid flannel shirt with the sleeves rolled up partly, and jeans. All of which seemed like they were moments from clinging to the timberwolf for dear life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the biggest attention grabber for the eyes was in what &lt;em&gt;wasn’t&lt;/em&gt; covered by the clothing; a smooth, soft gloss took the place of the normal fur of his hands, forearms, face, and even a bit peeking out from under the shirt. Was that…?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Er, y’alright there? Hope I didn’t uh, interrupt somethin’,” the wolf spoke softly. As his stance shifted, it elicited a faint ‘sqrk’, similar to the sounds during the cuddling session the night before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I...yeah, that’s me, sorry, um...who did you say your na-I mean, what did...yeah,” the coyote stumbled out before looking up to greet the wolf’s soft expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hah, I ain’t yet. ‘Name’s Brandon,” he replied, extending one of those thick handpaws to shake, which nearly swallowed Cody’s. &lt;em&gt;Rubber. It really is. Warm, soft rubber, not...solid?&lt;/em&gt; “Thomas over there said yuh were in a bit-of-a bind n'… well, I’ve known him a good while, n’ trust him t’ only point out someone ah can trust.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trust…? Thomas...me?” Cody asked. Words were hard at the moment as his brain tried critically to process the sight before him, and kept ending up in places that would embarrass him and nearly sent his face into a beet-red blush. But he kept it in check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh, he didn’t think ya’d drink much o’ that coffee yet, guess he was right,” the wolf replied with a chuckle, as he walked around the row of chairs to take a seat in the empty one to Cody’s side. The heady scent of latex was absolutely unmistakable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody kept silent for a moment as he followed Brandon’s steps, looking briefly down to catch sight of his paws in a similar open-foot shoe to the coyote’s, letting the glossy sheen of the paws and toes show, exposed as they were. “What’re…” he started, before shaking his head, and looking back up to Brandon. “Sorry, I uh…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timberwolf laughed, giving the coyote’s upper back a pat with one of those thick, glossy paws. “I get it, don’t worry yerself there; Thomas s’like that when ah first met him too. S’what you think exactly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody thought he might faint at the thought. “You’re really…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rubber, latex ah guess, n’ air, yeah. But uh, that aside fer the moment,” Brandon started. He struggled for words, before beginning. “Look, ah know I ain’t the smoothest when it comes t’ greetin’ folks fer somethin’ like this, usually that's just my hide, but I’ve got a proposition. My hauls are pretty long, n’ with how dark it gets this time of year, the drives are pretty borin’ n’ quiet. So, in exchange fer some company on the drives, yer free t’ ride along with me. No other ulterior motives, I promise. Tired o’ drivin’ alone, n’ I’d rather help a friendly fellah out than just anyone. Yer free to leave at any time – at least if we’re somewhere safe, ain’t about t’ letcha get off if we’re just somewhere in the middle of the woods...not that ah can really stop yuh but...y’know, wouldn’t be right o’ me to not try,” the wolf said, rubbing the back of his head lightly with a chuckle at the last bit, eliciting a few more rubbery squirks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody sat listening, his eyes slightly wide, but with a lightly tired laze he tried to push back. “You...want me to ride with you? On your truck?” he asked, only barely realizing he was just repeating the wolf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, basically. Ain’t gotta do anythin’ on the truck, unless yer handy n’ wanna if somethin’ happens. Look, I know this is a lot at once, so I ain’t gonna be surprised or upset if y’ say ‘no’. But I know how much it sucks t’ feel abandoned, n’ if I can help in some way and it gives me a lil company too…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“...Most folks I guess think you’re...well...this isn’t what &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; think but, ‘weird’?” Cody asked, wincing slightly as he realized how awkward that sounded. Not the fastest tonight, he thought, and took a sip of his coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yyyeah, guess so. N’ ah figured you wouldn’t, cause...well, wolves have a pretty good sense of smell, even like this,” Brandon replied. Cody’s toes curled slightly as his mask failed. No hiding that blush. “Besides, Thomas wouldn’t point me your way if he thought you’d be put off. And it’s...well, nice, fer stuff t’ be the opposite of that,” the wolf added, his own cheeks a touch pink as he spoke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That...fuck it. That sounds like a change of pace I need," Cody said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What’re you doing?’&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been wanting to see more of the Northern lands,” the coyote added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What’re you doing this’ll never work!’&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I...I don’t know what I’ve been waiting for, here,” Cody replied, swallowing as he did his best to ignore those thoughts. “Maybe this, this kinda thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon smiled, and let out a cheerful laugh. It was a warm sound, slightly reverberant, in a way that cemented the wolf’s description. Rubber and air. “What, some kinda adventure? Heh, can’t really say it’d be an adventure of a typical sort, but…” he extended his paw to shake again. “We’ll figure out anything as we go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody took that giant handpaw in both of his own, both to squeeze and lightly rub to confirm for himself a third time that his eyes weren’t deceiving him. Warm, soft, squeaky, squishy. “Uh...then, yeah, I guess so. As long as I won’t be in the way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not a bit. Grab what you need, and meet me at my truck out back. We’re gonna drive a bit further on t’night, it’s pretty early still, for me at least,” the wolf asked, holding up his own coffee. A gallon mug. The coyote figured he’d ask later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded, and felt a smile cross his muzzle for only the second time yet at the truck stop. “Yeah,” he replied, with another squeeze to the wolf’s paw before he released it, nodding again as Brandon stood, striding off towards the back of the store towards the trucker exit. As the wolf left, the coyote stood as well, letting out a deep sigh as residual tension left him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s got a heart of gold. I wouldn’t have pointed him toward you if I didn’t trust him,” came Thomas’s voice, causing the coyote to quickly turn to face the attendant. “Sorry, I guess you were too focused to hear me walk up. But I mean it,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where the hell did you even meet him?” the coyote asked, his voice quieter than usual. “What even…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He stopped in one night while I was working, and just kinda...hit it off well. He’s stopped in many times over the past couple years to say howdy and for a hug,” the ferret replied, rubbing the back of his own head with a slight sheepish expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You mean he smelled you stealthing and realized you’d be friendly?” the coyote teased. He felt lighter, easier, more at-ease than he had. “I’m teasing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And right,” Thomas laughed, shaking his head. “I know he’ll take good care of you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote stood, and after a brief pause, embraced Thomas in a tight hug the ferret returned. “Thank you. You’ve been incredibly sweet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can thank me by giving me another hug like that in a week; should be back by here then,” the ferret replied, releasing the hug and patting Cody’s sides. “Now grab a fresh hot coffee, and some food on me, and get on the road.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Snowbound</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/snowbound.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:57:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:57:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/snowbound.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Having accepted the offer to ride along with Brandon, Cody sets off with the rubber wolf, with a cozy end to the night again.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Gack!” Cody shook his paw to free it of the snow that’d fallen off, and grasped the door handle again to swing it open, hinges creaking lightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, there y’are! Was uh, hopin’ you didn’t get cold feet. Moreso n’ the snow caused,” Brandon said, smiling across at the coyote who clambered up into the cab and seat, shaking off his paws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only from the snow. Do you have a towel I could borrow?” Cody asked, gratefully accepting one handed over to dry his footpaws after settling into the seat and closing the door. “Just wanted to get a little...er...cleaned up,” he added, pausing with a faint sniff at the air in the cab, unable to hide the forming blush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sight got a chuckle out of the wolf as he worked the starter on the truck, bringing the engine to life with a roar. “If the smell in here’s gotcha blushin’ that bad, I think we’ll get on pretty good,” he added as he checked a few gauges, before easing the truck into first gear, and getting it rolling slowly towards the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded a little sheepishly, freeing his paws from the shoes to finish drying them thoroughly, after noticing Brandon had done the same, and then draped the towel over the back of his seat rest as indicated, pausing to look around the cab as well. He didn’t remember most trucks being nearly this spacious, but he never rode in a long-distance truck like this one. The chairs were custom, his own quite a bit larger than usual, but Brandon’s much wider to provide the large wolf a comfortable spot. They nearly touched. “I haven’t been in one that didn’t stink of sweat until now,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, well, ain’t ridden in one owned by a big’ ol’ rubber balloon of a wuff I guess either,” Brandon chuckled, facing the road as the truck picked up speed along the snowy highway. “But I don’t think this truck’ll ever stop smellin’ like balloon.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody smiled softly, as he leaned back into the chair to get comfortable. “What’s wrong with that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did I say there was anythin’ wrong with it?” the wolf asked with a grin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“True! So...you really are?” Cody asked, tentatively reaching toward the wolf, who offered up his right handpaw and tail after guiding it around the chair for the coyote to feel with the chairs nearly touching. He squeezed, careful of his claws, as he explored the smooth surfaces. He couldn’t help but to giggle slightly from the faint squeaks and squirks the attention elicited. He found he could squeeze any finger completely flat, or even flat into the palm. The tail was a little too puffy for him to do so without worrying about his claws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon seemed to enjoy the exploration, little rumbles from his chest reverberating lightly. “Yeah. A lot stretchier n’ more durable than your shorts, and whatever else you’ve got in that backpack,” he replied, briefly glancing at the coyote to show a teasing grin. “Which yer welcome t’ wear whenever you like between truck stops. I ain’t gonna judge, s’freein’ bein’ able to express in whatever way you prefer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody blushed even brighter red, as his ears tilted back slightly. “You sure?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, as long as it ain’t gonna make you freeze. Besides, it’d be kinda cute. But s’mostly for you. And yuh ain’t gotta worry about those claws,” the wolf replied while the coyote squeezed that tail again gently, prompting him to sink his paws in a little further.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It wouldn’t be...you sure that’s okay?” Cody asked, trying to be careful still.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If a would-be truck-jacker couldn’t pop me with his knife even when I was inflated to thrice this size, y’ain’t gonna do a damn thing with those claws. Feels nice anyway,” Brandon replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s eyes widened. There was no way the universe wasn’t just teasing him mercilessly at this point or this was anything more than a dream. He briefly pinched himself, just to check, before squeezing the tail...and then tentatively, reaching over to give it a hug, nosing into the tip with a deep inhale, and a shaky, happy sigh. He nearly went limp as every muscle relaxed at once, for the first time in what felt like months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shucks, y’like it that much?” Brandon asked, his own cheeks a touch pink. “Heh, guess I never thought of my tail helpin’ someone relax.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmh, is..kinda that...kinda...I dunno,” the coyote replied, as his eyes closed in comfort. “I...hope this uh, isn’t too much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not at all. I’m just glad it helps. Or me, I guess,” Brandon replied with a sheepish chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody sat holding onto that tail like a cuddly pillow for a few moments in quiet, before he spoke. “It’s just hard to believe you’re real. That a thought I’d had years ago walks into the same truck stop I’m at, offers to take me along, and...is real,” he mused, slipping on the mild redundancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What, a big ol’ rubber wolf a fantasy you had?” Brandon asked with a tone the coyote knew meant to elicit a deep blush. Successfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anything. Anyone. Just… the idea of someone &lt;em&gt;like&lt;/em&gt; you. I don’t wanna be too weird or something, I just got out of...sorry, I won’t ramble on,” Cody replied, his voice a little shaky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon paused, then reached over to rest his right handpaw on the back of the coyote’s head, keeping focus on the road. “We got a couple hours, and I ain’t got much to share to speak of. Y’ain’t gonna weird me out. It’s...really flattering, honest. Tell me what you want to, and about what happened? If you’re ready to,” the wolf spoke, his voice softer, gentler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody continued in silence for another minute, before he finally spoke. “I’ll...I’ll go into more detail later. Maybe. But I moved up from the Southern Desert to move in with my ex. Never had so much fur til I moved here. And it...didn’t work out. For a few reasons. One being him just not being okay with what you already told me you’d like. Said it embarassed him in front of his friends for me to dress shiny.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon’s paw slipped further to the coyote’s shoulder, guiding him to scoot to the edge of the seat, and lean into the wolf’s side. It really did feel like a balloon under clothes; a very thick balloon, but with that characteristic yield and bounce. “How’d stuff work out before that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, it was sunshine and rainbows over messaging, at least I thought it was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Long-distance?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah. LDR. I...don’t want to get into the weeds of it right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf’s embrace tightened a moment, and Cody’s toes curled feeling that soft rubber under the outfit yield against him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Thank you,” Cody added after another few seconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For a crappy side-hug?” Brandon asked with a chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll take a bigger hug later if you still wanna. But, I mean...well, all of this,” Cody answered as he gazed out the windshield. Snow flew past as the truck rumbled along, and passed the last in a series of road lamps, ahead stretching a seemingly endless darkness. He felt the wolf’s embrace tighten for a moment in response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon was silent as he focused for a minute. “S’the least I can do,” he answered, briefly rubbing between Cody’s ears. “Now, what all interesting didja fit in that backpack?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ll bake it up for you if we end up stopping somewhere with a kitchenette or oven, maybe even a toaster oven,” Cody laughed, smiling up at the chuckling wolf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Don’t think a toaster oven would hold enough mac to satisfy me, much less have any for you,” Brandon replied with a chuckle. “There’s a stop, can dip into the Door-mart beside it for supplies, that’s got an oven, and…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody chuckled along, but the pause got a pause out of him as well, and his expression eased as the wolf’s eyes narrowed slightly. “What is it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Downed trees ahead from the storm,” the wolf replied with a sigh, grasping the gear shift in his free paw. “Guess we’re stopping here for the night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody squinted to look into the dark ahead, barely making out the couple of trees, a larger one having pushed over two smaller ones when it fell. “Out...here?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon nodded as he slowed the truck, the brakes groaning as he eased towards the side of the road as the truck approached the trees. “Ain’t the first time fer me, not by a long shot. The chair reclines, n’ there’s space in the back,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody sat back in the passenger seat while watching the snow. “Space?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf nodded, while the truck loosed one last long squeak from the brakes as it came to a stop, with a hiss as the pressure in the lines released. Brandon killed the engine. Only the buffeting of the wind and the soft tinkle of settling snow filled the cab for a few seconds. “Might be uh...bit cozy, heh, but should be enough."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded, as the wolf got up to slip behind the seats, and pull aside the curtains covering the entrance to the back cab. A wide cot made for a bed, with inset drawers housing the wolf’s clothes it appeared, a stray shirt edge peeking out of one. “Cozy is uh...an understatement,” he chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon laughed, following Cody from behind, pausing as the round belly pressed into the coyote’s back. “Yeah...guess yer right. I’ll uh, grab a blanket fer myself up front,” he replied, shimmying in with a series of soft rubbery squeaks in scooting alongside the coyote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody paused, then placed a paw on Brandon’s side. “No, you…don’t need to do that. We can both fit. I’m pretty skinny without the jacket on. If er...you...are okay with that,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf chuckled. “I don’t mind. I’m comfortable with a lot. S’long as yer not gettin’ frisky… but Thomas said y’weren’t, and...well...did say you’re awfully cuddly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody smiled with a soft blush on his cheeks, visible in the dim glow of the back cab. “I’d...I think I’d like that. It was nice having that last night. And I definitely don’t mind tonight. Even if, um…” the coyote paused, looking to Brandon’s middle for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon watched the coyote’s gaze, and after a moment, he grinned. After reaching into the front cab to flick a switch, turning off the lights to it, he reached into the bin to the side to pull out a large blanket and settled it over the foot of the cot. He couldn’t help but to brush against the coyote lightly then as he wiggled to slip free of his flannel over shirt, and the white tee under it raised above his head, revealing that smooth, slightly glossy middle to the coyote. “Jeans too?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody blinked, taken from his gaze up and down the wolf’s rubbery form to blush up to him. “Wha?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf chuckled. “I’ll take that as a yes,” he replied, those thick rubbery paws working the belt buckle and button to loosen his jeans, and drop them down on the floor, keeping a pair of black undershorts on that appeared to be lycra. Disrobed, he shivered from the cooler air, and pulled the curtain into the front cab closed, before flopping back onto the cot..and patting his puffy middle while looking towards the coyote. “Now hurry up, it’s cold.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote’s red cheeks couldn’t be hidden, and he fidgeted a moment. As his thoughts tumbled, he didn’t even think to be surprised at the lack of negative thoughts. “Sleeping...&lt;em&gt;on&lt;/em&gt; you?” he asked, but already started to undress as well, jacket, then shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’d like to hope I’ll be a comfier balloon to sleep on than any you’ve slept on before,” the wolf replied, smiling warmly as the black latex of the coyote’s shorts shone in the dim light once Cody’s jeans slipped off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody paused, as if to find logistics, before simply placing one paw onto Brandon’s middle, and launching himself slightly with a hind foot, nearly losing his grip before the wolf’s strong grasp steadied him. “Thanks,” he mumbled, before replying further. “I’ve...never actually done that before. I was always afraid to pop them,” he said, as he adjusted himself on his knees, and finally leaned forward to rest his weight against Brandon’s middle, first lightly, and then in entirety. He felt like he was in heaven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like I said, ain’t gotta worry about that with me, pup. Er...sorry, heh. Just...awful cute like that,” the wolf replied, sheepishly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s okay. I don’t think anyone’s called me that,” Cody replied, as he shifted a footpaw to hoist the blanket edge up to where he could grab it, and pull it further over the pair, shimmying further up Brandon’s middle until his head was resting atop the wolf’s chest, and his arms spread to the side. The fact he couldn’t even reach the cot around the wolf made him wiggle a little. “You’re not uncomfortable?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon shook his head with a soft smile up to the coyote, before reaching to flick off the light, only a dim glow illuminating the space from some unseen LED. “Hard to make me uncomfortable, physically at least. And otherwise, well…” he paused, and slid both of his arms up around Cody’s back to hug the coyote to himself, who eagerly squeezed in return. “Guess we’re both pretty cuddly canines,” he chuckled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nudged his nose into the rubber trucker’s chest, sniffing at that latexy scent again. The best he’d ever smelled. Entirely exactly what it was and yet...alive, unique. Warm. “Yeah, this...this is really nice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf smiled brightly, and leaned up to press his nose affectionately between Cody’s ears. “Yeah...it is.” Silence filled the space, aside from the muffled howls of the wind, and occasional rubbery groan of the wolf’s frame as he shifted. After a few minutes, he spoke again. “Cody?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All of this...it’s not...too weird, to you, right? Promise me you’ll tell me if I do anything too weird or uncomfortable. I don’t...wanna make you want to leave.” ^8f2b68&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote’s grip tightened for a moment around the wolf’s middle. He involuntarily gave a warm lick against the trucker’s chest. “I promise I’ll tell you. And I promise it’s not too weird. Not in a bad way. It’s definitely weird, but, in a good way. Really good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like what you mentioned earlier?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Earlier?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“About… fantasies about guys like me. Tell me about that? It’s a big jump from liking latex into that.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody shifted about on Brandon’s middle, as his paws trailed along the wolf’s sides slowly. “I don’t know. Like, where it comes from. The idea. It just kept recurring, and every time with a little more detail. I like latex, I like guys wearing latex, but somehow the idea of a guy who &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; it, especially, well...air-filled, like you, hugging me, holding me. It’s been this lingering fantasy for a long time,” he replied, slowly, as his thoughts organized. “And likewise, that’s not too weird, is it?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon’s chuckle wobbled his frame slightly in the dark. “S’kinda fun, actually. It feature anything...else, about those kind of guys?” he asked, then practically giggled as the coyote’s grasp tightened in response. “We’ll see what happens,” he replied, “Get some rest, pup; it’s another long drive tomorrow.” With that, another creaky lean planted a quick peck between the coyote’s ears, before the wolf laid back to rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody let himself go slack in his cuddled embrace. Soft, puffy, warm, pillowy, everything felt amazing in the moment. The wolf’s soft breathing slowed into a quiet snore once in a while. As Cody closed his eyes, and let himself start to drift off, he quietly mumbled as if to the wolf. “...Why couldn’t I find you first?” Before any thought could answer, only soft snores filled the cab, as the blizzard howled on around them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Debris</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/debris.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:56:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:56:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/debris.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After the storm, Brandon gets to work clearing the road of fallen trees, including making short work of a big one in a way that flusters Cody tremendously.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cody awoke, gently at first. He didn’t remember falling asleep on a balloon, but it felt really nice to nuzzle his snout and face into, and he sighed happily. The balloon starting to pet along his back jogged his memory, and he squeezed a little tighter into the big rubber middle under him. “Mmm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sleep well there? Was s’prised y’ didn’t stir when I did,” the rubber trucker murmured, continuing a slow brushing through Cody’s fur with those soft, rubbery clawtips, from nape down to the coyote’s mid-back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody wasn’t sure he’d ever felt claws so wonderful before. “Guess I did, yeah. Thank you. You didn’t need to do that,” he mumbled in return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon snorted. “Like hell y’were gonna sleep up in the front by yerself, cold or no. Besides, y’ make fer a nicer blanket than that one.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody giggled at the thought, and smiled up towards Brandon, the wolf’s features visible most in the slight glossy sheen lit from what daylight filtered through the curtain. “I guess I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt; fluffier than it.” This was different. This was nice. He never got to wake up this cozily before. “So, uh, what’re we doing today?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon raised his arms up with a loud squirking of rubber as they brushed his sides and stretched, literally by a couple inches, before relaxing them. “Well, once y’ get off me and I get dressed, I’m gonna haul th’ trees outta the way, and we’ll find breakfast.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody raised an eyebrow. “You? Do...you need help? I’m not very strong but-”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Y’think this size is just fer show? I ain’t even inflated any bigger n’ normal right now. Don’tcha worry,” Brandon replied with a grin, huffing in, and spreading easily a few inches in all directions under Cody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote was grateful it wasn’t bright enough to see his blush. At least, he thought. “Oh, fuck,” he mumbled, shifting to ease back onto his knees on the cot, and off of Brandon’s middle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf grinned even wider and chuckled. “You’re gonna make it too easy t’ have fun with you, y’know,” he rumbled as he shifted up into a sitting position, and then hopped down to the floor of the truck, stretching his arms again overhead. “Get dressed however y’ like, but’s pretty cold. Shouldn’t be but half an hour or so t’ clear things up,” he added as he stepped into his jeans, tugging them up those tree-trunk legs easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded as he watched the wolf dress, a larger set of clothes than the ones he’d worn the night before, before opening the curtain to slip into the front cab, with a little more effort than he’d needed before too. He waited as Brandon managed to get the driver door open, the sounds of snow piles clattering precipitating a curse from the wolf, and squeaked outside. He looked around the cab, then back to the cot, and smiled. “I don’t wanna inconvenience him...but I kinda wish I could sleep like that every night,” he murmured, before turning to his backpack to fish around, and grinned as he grabbed something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fishing his paw out revealed a black latex t-shirt that glistened with a slight chlorinated sheen. He wiggled his arms up into it to pull over his head, grumbling as he felt his fur matte under it, but he smoothed it out with a few brushing rubs as he tugged it on. He reached in again, retrieving a black plaid flannel shirt, not unlike the ones the wolf wore, and pulled it on as well, leaving it unbuttoned in front. Finally, he tugged his own jeans up, and slipped into the front cab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world was white. Just white. Until his eyes adjusted and he realized it was all the snow settled on the windshield. Rather than fight with the passenger door, he took the driver’s side as Brandon had, and hopped down onto the road. The snow crunched under his paws with the landing, and he looked around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;White, but in a different way. The blizzard stopped at some point, though the skies were still deeply overcast. Everything was covered in a thick layer of snow, and sometimes ice, from the glistening sparkles on some of the pines along the road. As Brandon stepped out of the woods, heading for the treefall from the night before, Cody made his way over, every footstep crunching through the frozen layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon grasped one of the smaller trees around the bare trunk, and grunted as he hefted it up easily. At least, as easily as one would expect a big, burly 10ft-tall wolf, were he not made of rubber. And yet, heft he did. As he turned towards the woods again, his gaze passed over Cody, and he smiled, then blinked. “Y’ain’t cold?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody could only marvel, too distracted by his inflatable chaperone’s size to hear at first, before shaking his head. “No, why would I be?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Y’just got on that! I’m freezin’ out here, s’gonna be pretty warm once I start th’ truck up, brrf,” the wolf replied, heading towards the woods again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody followed. “You’re...cold? But you were pretty warm feeling overnight.” He looked down at himself, poking at his shirt. He was a little cold around there from his fur being compacted by the shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Freezin’. Heh, guess ah fergot what it’s like havin’ fur t’ keep warm,” replied the wolf, who dropped the tree down with a grunt alongside another. “F’we had time n’ I had the tools, could turn this into firewood.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody blinked, poking his own shirt again, rubbing around. Even with the latex squeezing, while it itself was very cold, his fur underneath still provided an insulating layer. “Guess that’s why I made for a good blanket,” he replied, following Brandon back out to the remaining tree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon paused in thought. “...Something like that. Maybe mostly cause you cuddle like you mean it,” he said, before continuing on towards the road again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody paused as he watched the wolf, tossing the thought in his head. Like he means it? The tone was a warm one, not as if he was frustrated at all. He shrugged before hurrying to catch up to the wolf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest tree was wider than the coyote was tall. Brandon studied it for a moment, then grumbled. “Gonna freeze my ass off even more fer a minute, but s’alright,” he mumbled, and as the coyote approached, he turned, slipping off his shirt with a shiver and handing it to Cody. “Least it ain’t windy. Hold these?” he added, the jeans promptly joining the shirt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody stood there in confusion, until the wolf took a deep breath, and the coyote widened his eyes as he watched that balloon of a middle surge outward, not centimeters, but over a meter, nearly two in width. The entire wolf’s torso joined it in the process, and as he bit his own thumb and ‘blew’, so too did the wolf’s height and breadth surge out with an array of rubbery squeaks and groans that sent the coyote’s ears pinning back to hide how red they were. “Holy shit,” he whispered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon turned to look down to Cody, and grinned. “Guess all th’ cold n’ trouble’s worth it t’ show off to y’, cutie,” he rumbled, as he repeated the gesture, a further powerful inhale heard rushing with those bellowing groans of his rubber hide as that waist ballooned in width, two, three, nearly four meters, before he blew on his thumb again to send his size burgeoning outward, rising in just as much height in a rapid rise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody couldn’t suppress the soft whine at the sight. “Fuck fuck fuck, this can’t be real, this is too fucking hot to be real,” he whispered to himself, but the smell of the wolf’s warm rubber, more intense than before, reassured him of the reality. “Outgrow the fucking truck,” he added, even more quietly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As if the wolf heard him anyway, or just to show off even more, Brandon’s inhale almost roared as the wolf drew in a breath that sent his entire middle billowing wildly, 6 meters, 8 meters, 10, before he blew again with enough force to blow his own cheeks up as his frame ballooned in size wildly, like a balloon attached to too powerful a pump, nearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s legs shook as he looked &lt;em&gt;up&lt;/em&gt; at the rubber wolf towering over him. The rubber trucker’d blown himself up til the truck was only as big as one of the wolf’s enormous legs. He pinched himself again. It seemed impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon grinned back down, and squeaked heavily with movement as he settled down into a sitting position before the coyote, offering a paw that the coyote found himself stepping into, before being hoisted up to the wolf’s chest. “How’s that?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody tried not to keep cursing in response to everything, almost dazed with the rush of movement and the incredible sight before him. And as he leaned into Brandon’s chest, he gasped. “Holy fucking shit...that’s fucking incredible, that’s what that is. You...you feel almost softer than you did last night.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon’s laugh nearly deafened the coyote, as he grinned, and brought his snout in, carefully touching his rubber nose to the coyote’s, dimpling his own inward around it slightly. “Toldja y’weren’t gonna pop me with them claws. Still wouldn’t like this. Biggest I’ve been’d be a little too hard to play with yuh.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“N-no no, this...is intensely hot. Sorry I just...I’m having a little...trouble processing it.” Cody replied, breathlessly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh, s’alright. It’s pretty damn cold this big, too much cold air,” Brandon rumbled, as he lowered his paw back to the ground, for the coyote to hop off. Turning, the wolf grabbed the tree as if it were just any other big stick, and tossed it to the side, where it crashed loudly into the undergrowth before it came to a stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody merely watched, and approached slowly, as the wolf dusted his paws and started to exhale, a torrent of air pouring out, disturbing some misty swirls in the cold as he shrank back down in size, surprisingly fast, though he looked a touch...underinflated, for a moment, as he reached near his normal size. Cody held out the wolf’s clothes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon gratefully accepted them, pulling his jeans on first, and then the shirt, shivering. “Guess the cold’s affectin’ my hide a bit. Might be better t’ wait til it’s a lot warmer before I go for bigger again,” he laughed, striding back towards the truck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I...yeah, whatever is best, I’m just…” Cody breathed, before Brandon patted him on the back, drawing him up against the wolf’s side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hehe, s’alright, I...may’ve reacted about th’ same when I first started t’ explore it,” the wolf chuckled, before helping Cody up into the truck on the driver’s side, and followed him up, quickly bringing the engine to life with a chug, and then a roar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody settled into his own seat again, watching the wipers start to plow the snow off the windshield. “Yeah.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the windshield finished clearing, the wolf worked the gearbox again, easing the truck back onto the road, as clumps of accumulated snow fell and splashed on the hood of the truck, splattering into bursts of white. “Y’alright?” Brandon asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody simply nodded, looking down at his own shirt, and touching it again, feeling the cold rubber slowly warm. &lt;em&gt;What’s it like? Being like that?&lt;/em&gt; “Yeah, I’m...just a little overwhelmed. In a good way. Really good, just…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf chuckled, and slipped his free paw under the coyote’s overshirt, to rest on the back of the rubber shirt. Cody swore he could feel it better than against his bare fur. “Sorry ‘bout that, guess I got a lil’ carried away,” Brandon rumbled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You’re fine. I was encouraging it anyway,” Cody chuckled, looking up to the wolf. “Anyway. Is it a longer stretch today cause of the stop?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon nodded as the truck barreled down the road, the heavy, studded tires finding their tread with every inch. “Yeah, an hour or so. Plan is to stop at a truck stop in Burla that has plenty of stuff. Get breakfast, stock up, shower up, n’ hit the road.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote perked his ears up halfway through. “...Breakfast?”&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Go-Go Juice</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/go-go-juice.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:55:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:55:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/go-go-juice.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After Brandon's brief showing off, the two find breakfast. A short cheerful chapter, with Brandon talking a bit about his rubbery biology.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The plates clunked with a dull thud as the waitress placed several steaming dishes on the table before the pair. “Full spread with cinnamon bread, and a double waffle with eggs for you, darlin’. Anything else I can get for ya right now?” the husky asked, brushing her paws on her apron.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Um, some more coffee would be lovely, thank you,” Cody replied, with a soft smile up to her.
The waitress smiled, quickly returning with the carafe to refill his mug. “Brandon, you’re gonna get sick if you order anything sweet from me, ya got enough of that here with this cutie,” she scolded in a teasing tone, causing the coyote to look away in embarrassment and the wolf to laugh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Only if yuh don’t scare him off first. Don’t worry about her, next time she’ll probably flip sides in the ribbing,” the wolf chuckled as the waitress walked off, and started to dig into one of his plates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody looked down at the food, and rubbed a paw through the fluff of his nape, pausing as he brushed the collar of the latex shirt hidden under his hoodie. “Guess I’m not used to that yet,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Maybe, y’strike me as someone who ain’t unfamiliar with it, jus’...more of ‘not a good time’ kinda?” the wolf started, though his own ears laid back slightly. “Er, sorry.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody chuckled softly, taking another sip of his coffee. “No, it’s...it’s fine. I mean it. I guess it’s like a weird fluctuating thing,” he assured as he picked up the butter cup, blanched at the margarine tubs, and grabbed the syrup instead to drizzle over the waffles. “But it helps? Like...being somewhere. Not stuck.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon started to muffle something through his food before he thought better of it given the pause and large swig of his own coffee. “Yeah? Y’know, if there’s anywhere y’wanna head after the delivery t’morrow, we’ve got a day er two for whatever b’fore the next pickup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody smiled softly at the offer, after chewing down a big forkful of his waffle, coughing at first at the oversized bite before he could reply. “Not like that, I mean just...out. Anywhere. I dunno, but yeah, thank you. I’ll try to think of somewhere.” He paused. “You never answered in the truck about the whole uh...’eating’ thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon chuckled, leaning forward on an elbow that squeaked on the table top. “I ain’t had to, I think. But I guess I end up turnin’ it into uh...I dunno. More ‘me’?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That’s usually what happens with food, yes,” Cody giggled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf rolled his eyes. “Not like that, ya goof. Like uh...I guess more liquid rubber or whatever for...uh...things...and makes me stretchier. Softer. Not like I ain’t already, but...more is always fun. Especially for an appreciative ‘yote like you, pup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody looked down to hide the reddening visible even through his fur over his cheeks, with a brief huff he tried to muffle with another bite, only to cough again. “...You’re mean,” he mumbled after swallowing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hopefully in a good way?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded in response with a squirm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon grinned. “Ain’t used to uh...flirtin’ or whatever yuh call it like that, so uh, if I say somethin’ dumb, just know it’s meant in a friendly way,” he admitted, returning to his plate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“So you only eat sometimes?” the coyote asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Pretty much. Coffee seems t’ do the same thing as anyone. But last time I ate was a couple days ago. And I don’t wantcha skippin’ any meals, so guess you gotta put up with the, uh, results,” the wolf replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody considered this for a moment as he dug into his food more. &lt;em&gt;He’s really worried about me.&lt;/em&gt; ‘Well you can’t take care of yourself.’ He shook his head briefly to clear the thought as he dug in further, catching sight of but not processing the wolf’s brief look of concern. “Don’t think ‘put up with’ is the right phrasing for something like that,” the coyote finally said with a chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Nightgown</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/nightgown.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T23:54:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T23:54:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/nightgown.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Settling into a hotel after a day of driving, the two find calm, allowing Cody a place to open up a little bit about the scars of his trauma. I'm still not 100% good with this chapter but mostly happy.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Is it weird I don’t know if this kind of snowfall or the blizzard are prettier?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon turned as the key clicked in the lock, looking down to Cody. “Hmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Like, it’s pretty. At least at night like this. Was prettier where we parked, without the street lights, just dim moon,” the coyote added, tugging lightly at the bare rubber tee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon chuckled as he swung the door inward. “Get inside first, it’s damn cold, n’ we can kill the lights and leave the blinds open,” he said as he nudged the coyote with a thick paw squeaking against the coyote’s shirt and earning a quick ‘yip’ from him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, okay,” Cody said as he slipped on in, the wolf following him to close the door, closing the sliding latch at the top. The coyote looked around, sniffing briefly, before padding to the closer side of the king-sized bed to plop his backpack down, reaching into it to fetch his phone charger while the wolf followed through in opening the blinds, and dropping his own duffel on the table in the motel room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There we are. Ain’t gotta sleep yet but..” the wolf slipped out of his own over and under shirts, dropping them on the chair back. “C’mere,” he added, patting the top of the bed on the coyote’s side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody couldn’t help a soft smile, taking a seat first, and then leaning back into the wolf’s middle as Brandon situated himself to be a stable cushion for the coyote, and draped an arm around him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf chuckled at the soft squeak from the coyote’s shirt against his own rubbery hide. “Comfy? Good view?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded, and leaned back slightly further. The wolf hadn’t been kidding; he felt even softer, nearly like an underinflated balloon he could sink into, making it much easier to cushion him. “Yeah… ‘put up with’ was definitely not the right phrasing earlier,” he replied with a soft snrk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon chuckled, and tightened the arm around the coyote. “Figured it wasn’t. But good view?” he asked again, reaching with his free paw to click the switch beside the bed, turning off the lamps. The only light came through the window, framing the soft falling flakes, dense, but without the insistent rush of the blizzard the night before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody quietly nodded, wrapping an arm around the wolf’s in kind, to hug to himself, before finding the wolf’s tail to hug up alongside himself in his lap, quietly content to the soft squeaks of his outfit and the wolf’s form as he watched the frigid display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not weird at all,” Brandon whispered in Cody’s ear after a long moment of silence. “Not a bit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded faintly, and tightened his grip around Brandon’s tail with a few more squeaks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Did he call you weird?” Brandon asked after another brief pause.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody twitched slightly. “Mm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon’s nose brushed the back of the coyote’s head softly, between his ears. “Or they? She? Figured ‘he’ though.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody kept looking at the window, pausing, muzzle audibly opening and closing two times before he simply nodded softly. “He.” It was quiet, a little strained. Cody knew he was bad at hiding that. The wolf’s nose brushed gently from one ear to the other, and the coyote inhaled deeply through his nose, though with a quicker involuntary sniff at the end, followed by a slightly shaky exhale. It and the rubbery scent were...comforting, somehow. Only now did Cody realize that the wolf’s latexy hide smelled slightly differently from his tee. Warmer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Shh…s’alright. I’m not gonna get upset atcha fer cryin’,” Brandon murmured in the coyote’s ear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How’d…?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon shifted slightly onto his hip to balance as he wrapped his other arm around Cody’s front, to hold to himself. “Because I felt it drip on my tail.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Oh.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hey, is alright. I promise. And promise y’ain’t weird. Not fer likin’ the snow, not fer liking wearin’ what yer wearin’, not fer skippin’ the fake butter on yer waffles, and certainly not fer liking bein’ with me,” the wolf spoke softly, giving each of the coyote’s ears a quick peck at the base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody turned away from the window to bury his face into Brandon’s chest, even nuzzling in for the material to stretch around his muzzle slightly in an effort to be even closer. “He got mad at me for wanting to wear it even when his friends weren’t over. And that I’d pull on something else or take it off when he wanted to smoke. He didn’t even hate it, he liked me wearing it but just...not...outside of the bedroom,” he mumbled, head tilted to the side slightly to be heard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf’s grip tightened. “Well it ain’t dumb or weird. Despite bein’ me, it normally ain’t like, a thing, but… it’s pretty cute on you. It looks good. But most importantly, it ain’t weird or dumb,” he spoke, more firmly by the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Even not wanting to smoke with his friends?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon snorted. “Well, passin’ on free weed’s a little weird, but-”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He wanted me to pay for more than I would’ve used.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well fuck him then. Fuck that. But based on whatcha said so far, I wouldn’t blame yuh fer not wantin’ to with him at all, much less his friends,” the wolf added. “Nor it puttin’ ya off it entirely, fer that matter.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody tightened his own embrace to sink further into that pillowy warm wolf-rubber. “Thank you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon smiled softly, resting his snout between the coyote’s ears. “I’m just tellin’ the truth.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote shook his head, though he giggled briefly from the squeaking of rubber on rubber the movement caused. “No, not just that. You saved a moody coyote from being stuck, dumped at a truck stop, and you’re asking me about...me. It means a lot more than you realize.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf was quiet for a moment, before he spoke up. “My last relationship was a few years ago. He liked that I was a big guy n’ strong. But the moment I ended up like this, he was embarrassed to be around me in public. It wasn’t ‘as fun’ to him as when I was heavier. We split not long after,” he rumbled, whilst brushing a paw slowly down the coyote’s nape and back, finding a smoother path with a little more polish that reduced the amount of squeaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Conditional,” the coyote mumbled softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon nodded. “Basically. Didn’t invite his friends over, n’ didn’t wanna go anywhere public when I was home b’tween truckloads,” he confirmed, as he nudged the coyote’s forehead. “Tellin’ yuh t’ help...empathize? That I know what it’s like t’ feel excluded fer bein’ ‘weird’. And y’ain’t that a bit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded against Brandon’s chest, and then rolled against his hip to lean back into the wolf and watch the window again. “Camping.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hmm?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Can we go camping somewhere?” Cody asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon paused, then chuckled warmly. “You wanna go camping while it’s snowin’?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded, smiling to himself softly. “I miss doing it. He hated the cold, period, only went camping once.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon’s arm tightened around the coyote again. “Then we’ll find somewhere t’ camp,” he replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s tail flopped lightly. “Can...I sleep on you, when we do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf laughed, and settled onto his side alongside the coyote, to cuddle him up in a squeaky spooning. “Was I really that comfy?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody giggled. “Yeah. I’ll find a blanket big enough for both of us if you get big enough to-”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“-use my entire tum as an air mattress?” Brandon asked, ruffling a paw over the coyote’s middle, eliciting squeaks from the shirt contact and squirmy giggles from the tickled coyote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ehehe stop! Yeah, hehe, that,” the coyote replied, his footpaws scrabbling at the top quilt under them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf grinned, and nosed in to plant a quick kiss atop Cody’s head, more audible than the briefer pecks from before. “I’d absolutely love for ya to do that, pup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not tonight?” the coyote asked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you want any hope of gettin’ up t’ pee at 4 AM here, then I shouldn’t get much bigger. I’ll get carried away otherwise… also don’t uh, wanna break anythin’ in here,” Brandon replied sheepishly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody laughed with the protest, and wiggled to cozy up further with the wolf. “I’ll letcha off the hook &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; time, then,” he replied playfully, smiling as he watched the falling flakes rustle from a brief gust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wolf chuckled as well, tightening his arms around Cody, and shifting with multiple loud rubbery groans as he brought the coyote into a sitting position within his own lap. “First thought you were gonna smell like my rubber fer weeks, but I’m rubbin’ off on ya with my accent already? Sheesh,” he teased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody leaned back further, letting out a slow, shaky sigh of relaxation. “Doesn’t sound too bad,” he said, eyes closed slightly. “Pretty good, really.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The passing minutes built a small white leanto against the window of icy flakes, glistening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cody?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mmmh?”, the coyote grunted softly, stirring. “Was I snoring?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon shook his head, and leaned forward, letting his rubbery chest deform and stretch around Cody’s shoulders, to rest his head atop the coyote’s. “Nah. Or I didn’t hear it if yuh were.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody chuckled with a worn-out groan. “Mmh...guess I should get to sleeping properly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon nodded softly, rocking his muzzle atop the coyote’s ears. “Yeah,” he murmurred after a pause, and helped Cody lift the latex t-shirt off, setting it to the side before scooting on under the covers alongside him after kicking off his own jeans to follow the coyote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Cody found himself nestling up to the rubber wolf, his eyes closed again, and he let out a soft, content whine from the sense of comfort, cuddled up on the bed. He thought he heard “thank you” from the wolf, but hadn’t even a moment to ponder it before dreams took him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Winter-time End-of-year wishes</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/winter-time-end-of-year-wishes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-24T16:25:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-24T16:25:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-12-24:/articles/2023/winter-time-end-of-year-wishes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;With many friends of many faiths, and especially myself not being religious, I don't quite feel right wishing anyone a "Merry Christmas", nor a "happy holidays", as I don't want to seem like I'm co-opting a holy month of the year for many. But I still want to share &lt;em&gt;something …&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;With many friends of many faiths, and especially myself not being religious, I don't quite feel right wishing anyone a "Merry Christmas", nor a "happy holidays", as I don't want to seem like I'm co-opting a holy month of the year for many. But I still want to share &lt;em&gt;something.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winter's always been a fairly special time for me less for holidays as holy days, but more the season being unique-feeling, snow, time with family, visits, and sharing love with people I care about. Presents were always nice as a kid of course, but I don't think about them much now. I'm just appreciative of things at any time of year, and so Christmas-time is more of "winter holiday" for me. It's why I also want to do cookies in January, because I want to give people cheer where I can, something nice. Seasonal affective sucks, and if I can help others having it any and combat my own in the process, all the better! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just want everyone to have a wonderful winter time, especially if spent with family, and if they're in need of some form of cheer, that they can find it, whether through born family, chosen family, friends, or even strangers. Take time for you during these darker Northern months, or warmer Southern months, wherever you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big squeaky hugs from a puffy coyote who just wants to spread a few smiles if he can. 🧡🎈&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"></category><category term="christmas"></category><category term="holidays"></category><category term="winter"></category></entry><entry><title>New Job, Budding Hobbies, and Family Health</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-13T14:30:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T11:27:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-12-13:/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh god was this long to prep. I started writing this with the intent of it just being a blog update, and then got into getting Mastodon comments into this blog, fixing styling issues, fixing imports and dependencies so I could just use npm to install things...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...it was a …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh god was this long to prep. I started writing this with the intent of it just being a blog update, and then got into getting Mastodon comments into this blog, fixing styling issues, fixing imports and dependencies so I could just use npm to install things...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...it was a lot. Shit. I've nearly forgotten what I was gonna write. At least the subject's still staring at me, so...there's that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fair warning in advance, this post will contain talk about outsiders and family having critical health conditions as well as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll start off as it says in order, new job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;New Job&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;but we gotta start with the old&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;so first up, where I was and why it sucked&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting at the end of 2012, all the way up through mid-July of this year, I'd worked for the same company more-or-less -- shifting roles, company acquisitions, etc. I started in call center and eventually ended up a systems administrator for a healthcare software company, AKA, an independent medical review org, part of the reason why insurance sucks so much in the US. I'll refer to them as ShitPro in this post, it's vaguely like their name. For a long time I'd convinced myself that this role was OK, because most of ShitPro's clients were Medicaid (government-funded healthcare per-state, for those outside the US). The idea was that it was "saving them money" by "figuring out if doctors really tried everything they needed for patients", except a lot of times patients had to do the lifting with doctors to let them know drugs couldn't be filled, because doctors didn't think that their licensed practice of medicine would be second-guessed by a bunch of suits, rightfully so, and thus had not started a PA to begin with. I didn't fully understand it at first, but once I did, I think I convinced myself it was fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to early 2021, early 2022? I don't remember. In either case, I ended up, now a systems admin and handling technology that was used for all of ShitPro's clients (including &lt;strong&gt;private&lt;/strong&gt; health insurance now, ugh) fielding a request about a fax. The provider (doctor or hospital) in question blamed ShitPro for bungling an appeal for halting a hospital discharge. I'm not sure how that's something Medicare (federal-gov-paid healthcare) can do, but they apparently can, or something. Either way, I reviewed the case in question and found the fax &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; sent to ShitPro before the like, 2:30 PM or 3:00 PM deadline -- I dunno exactly, these deadlines are based on when the case is opened, not a specific time of day, it's fucked up. But it was only &lt;em&gt;started&lt;/em&gt; before that deadline, not completed, and because it's all digital, and faxes are a physically-analog process even when transmitted between digital services, the fax didn't complete for nearly 2 hours, pushing it an hour &lt;em&gt;past&lt;/em&gt; that deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was livid. I was talking to a coworker on a voice call who was able to help me track down with what she could see in her application, and she had a verbal shrug, because both of our hands were tied. I tried to reply back to the person entering the case, and they just cared "did ShitPro receive the fax file late due to no fault of ShitPro?" and unfortunately, the answer was a technical yes because the FTP server was fine, nothing had slowed it down other than the time it takes for a fax to transfer. Hell, if it was still paper, I bet they would've had the same fucking response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was more upset, it started sinking in how people were being affected. My walf was facing issues with PAs as well, through the other half of who ShitPro formerly was, split off in a merger, and I felt responsible &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; helpless at the same time. I wanted to make it right, I wanted to make things work, but I had no power to poke anyone who could do anything of consequence, and my role in contributing to the operation of these platforms, even without being the one making the decisions, started weighing very heavily on me. But I wasn't making enough to just leave or find something lower income to immediately switch to because of other financial obligations. So I sulked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A month later after the fax incident, I had a new ticket. "ManagerName is getting voicemails she's not supposed to get from emailsender". I reached out and had a sample email forwarded. Because these voicemails were to digital systems that transcribed, I was unable to avoid seeing the contents in trying to troubleshoot. It was too close to the areas I needed to look at. Even without playing the attachment I felt like I could hear the helpless voice of a woman trying desperately to keep getting her mother the hospital care she and doctors felt were needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even now this hurts to remember. I was crushed. I couldn't work the rest of the week. I was work-from-home, so no one could see me sitting on the couch all day instead. But the night of that I cried, sobbed in my walf's arms in a park I'd met up with him at to just get outside, get some fresh air at night. It was cold and I felt like the shittiest person on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I slowly managed to pull something together, but from then on, every day at my job for the next I dunno, year and a half, two years? Every day felt interminable. Every so often some task would come up that would snag that ADHD interest, that burned at the right synapses to engage me, but it wasn't often. I started hunting for a new job, but I barely had the energy to try, and unlike many of my friends, I don't have a specialized knowledge set. My knowledge in technology is very broad, with deeper areas in some places, but nothing like I felt like most places demanded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;the job hunt begins, slowly&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I met up with a former coworker, who also hated ShitPro for similar reasons, for a beer to talk about what his employer had available after learning about the roles. I was interested, and applied, but it turned out to be a dead end lead. My former coworker tried to find other ways to get me in, but they'd all require I take a pay cut first for an unknown amount of time before I could be moved to the team he was in. I passed, and started looking again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then a furry friend offered to refer me for the same team he was on, same position, at Indeed. It sounded fantastic on paper -- integrating employer talent programs and applicant tracking systems with Indeed's systems in a multitude of ways to make it easier for people to apply for jobs and for employers to review applications. It sounded great. And based on what the recruiter told me, I was the only other one when they selected someone else for the 'lead' role, after almost 10 interviews, due to lack of leadership experience. But I was told to apply again when a senior-level position opened. I kept tuned and attentive, and applied when I finally got notice it was open. I was ecstatic still, and the new recruiter called me and told me he was astounded they hadn't picked me last time based on the feedback he read from everyone who interviewed me. He wasn't sure what all they'd need to do since it was only a few months later, but promised a very high likelihood I'd net it just because of that. But 2 days later I got a call again, informing me that unfortunately the position was removed, no one accepted in, and Indeed was going on a hiring freeze for an unknown amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stuck again, I didn't really know what to do. I kept looking around here and there when I found energy. The success with Indeed had weirdly empowered me slightly, and started to make me angry at ShitPro, and want to find something better. Finally, I ended up looking at jobs at the university here, Auburn. I found several job positions I could do, though many I didn't want to do anymore (was exhausted with sysadmin work). But there were a few that piqued my interest, and I applied. Vordex, another local fur and fellow coyote, who works there, told me not to expect to hear back from them for a while, because his A/V role got a callback months later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;And finally forward motion&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got an email the next week, while at FWA 2023. They wanted to interview for a position that I was genuinely interested in, and I was very excited. That fast despite what I was told? I was really eager, and so were they, interviewing me literally less than a week later!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a great interview. I felt really good about things, I was unsure of myself in a few spaces due to lack of experience, but the courteousness with which everyone greeted me and talked to me gave me confidence that I could do what was needed, I could learn whatever I was missing to fill in those empty spots. I think 1-2 weeks later I got an email back asking for an in-person interview on campus, setting up to meet more people. I went in, sat down, and felt really nervous but good in talking to people. I was even asked if, because I don't have a degree, if I'd planned to use Auburn's free hours each semester to take classes while employed. I had no idea they had it, and said I'd absolutely do so because that was exciting too! I never finished, and I wanted to go back and try again, this time in an MIS role instead of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And about a week later I got a call from my new manager telling me that if I accepted the verbal offer, I'd be sent a written one to sign to become a university employee. I about cried in joy at this. I felt like shackles were breaking free that I'd been trapped with for so long I'd forgotten they were there. As soon as I signed the written offer with a start date, I put in my notice with ShitPro, and anxiety built with a need to &lt;em&gt;leave&lt;/em&gt; that place for good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;And the new job at last&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The folks who interviewed me ended up being pretty direct coworkers. One sits next to me, and I'm working with him closely on building out a new campus portal that's replacing the aging old one. The hiring manager is my direct manager, a guy who does much more work than management because he trusts the people under him, he works with us, and is a generally great guy. The 'exec' who'd asked about the tuition benefit is my boss's manager, also a very nice guy who's friendly each time he sees me. So many folks here know my name just from meeting in a good way early on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And even with a very slow start building over a few months, I feel useful. I feel wanted, needed here, not out of desperation, but because of valuing me. I'm doing work that makes student lives easier and helps faculty and staff as well. It feels almost like a penance for working for ShitPro for so long, but a penance I'm grateful for the opportunity to perform, and enjoying as well. The university's even queer-friendly as hell; there've been &lt;strong&gt;massive&lt;/strong&gt; diversity and inclusion improvements across all facets since I'd last known what the university had to offer. Once a month on a Friday I go with Vordex to have coffee with a bunch of other queer coworkers on campus, and it's fantastic. Sometimes it feels like a dream it's been so huge of an improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Remember that tuition benefit?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auburn offers employees of at least a year of service up to 5 hours of courses each semester paid by the university. Given my role, I had to be granted a student role in the application, allowing me to see that there was still an academic hold on my account preventing registration. I'd not been sure what to do, but about 2 weeks ago at queer coffee I heard the director of the pride center talking to someone about care she'd been giving in academic management to students who had trouble with it. Speaking up, I asked if she knew about academic holds, and she said she did, and figured what I was going to ask. I showed her the hold, and she asked for details. As I started to talk at first, I found I could pull up my unofficial transcript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the entire... 14 years? It was Spring 2007 when I left. In the whole time, I'd never looked at my grades for that second and final semester I had there until sitting there on campus again with someone who could help. And looking at a column of nothing but F's except for my men's chorus course welled up all those painful feelings I had buried for so long. I choked a little, but showed her. As we talked, I started to choke up more when she started talking to me about ways to address it. She said it'd be easy to work past, as long as I could maintain a per-semester average.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, given it was so bad for that one semester, she had another idea: retroactive medical discharge. My mental health was in the toilet that year, and I couldn't even bear going to classes most of the time. The combination of welling old pain, and a new sense of hope that I could erase that entire mark on my record and start as if it'd never happened? I don't know how I avoided sobbing from the mixture, I definitely wasn't able to hold back tears. She told me she would help me with the case, needing a letter from me to explain the need for medical discharge. So that's my next task for that, is work on that, to try and undo some of the pain of the past and start fresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that's where I am. You can see a little bit how all of this contributes to that feeling of it nearly being a dream, hah! I'm excited, I'm eager, and I have a drive to wipe out that pain and start anew on something I can better handle. And I want to take the classes, I want to learn more. I can even take them during work hours, why wouldn't I take that benefit? I'm really eager and excited now. 🧡&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Budding Hobbies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that that's out of the way, besides baking a lot more and having fun, I started getting more into 3D. This is probably gonna be a pretty short section by comparison ahaha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple months ago I started up a Blender course I was gifted. I'd never taken a course, and my previous attempts with Blender had been with that donut tutorial, which I couldn't reproduce for the life of me. It felt like I wasn't capable of learning as a result, but it turns out that tutorial just blows. Turns out &lt;a href="https://www.gamedev.tv"&gt;GameDev.TV&lt;/a&gt; have some fantastic instructors who don't act like they're some whizbang rockstar teaching you to be the same. I'm still working through the course, but he built fundamentals first, navigation, basic tools, and started into editing, starting out with an island and lighthouse. From there, it was on to building a modular dungeon with reusable parts, learning some more-advanced tooling for warping things slightly, for adjustments, cuts, mirroring, learning enough to start figuring out how to make low-polygon shapes and models. It's been incredible to learn! I genuinely feel like I'm getting a better sense of using Blender, and have already begun making minor changes to things, and even modeled myself a low-poly puffy crown to use in VR Chat!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've never been able to draw because of my dyspraxia, and while I know there's plenty of artists with it who make due, and do wonderful art, it's only ever been a frustration for me. Finally learning in a visual art that isn't impaired by that because of using tooling for changes has been phenomenal. I feel excited as I learn more, I've been able to actually take advantage of what I've learned like I said, and I feel like, with enough practice and learning, that I could eventually make custom models entirely like what folks see, and that REALLY excites me to be able to do! So, I'm continuing to push forward with glee for that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Family Health&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Figured that'd be a short section. So, family health really concerns only one person: my dad. And again, this gets medically-graphic, fair warning. No one dies but there &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; mention of death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I got a message from my mom on a Thursday talking about the weather, and then as &lt;strong&gt;nearly&lt;/strong&gt; an aside at the end, telling us (my sister and I) that dad was in the hospital, but don't worry! Both of us replied in shock, hospital is a big deal for a stay, why didn't she tell us? "Well your dad didn't want you to worry and didn't think it was a big deal." Chat, I think you can imagine what came next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By that Friday night, my mom texted us to say that the doctors were keeping him because his pneumonia was so bad, and his O2 was so low, that they had to intubate him. He was put into a medically-induced coma to let his lungs recover. But over the weekend, each day the news was worse and worse. That Monday morning my mom texted us to say that the doctors weren't sure why he wasn't responding to medications, but were going to give him steroids, as... a "last ditch effort". I like to hope it was not that dire. I don't know the reality, and likely never will. And I'm kinda glad for that. But that night, my mom voice-called myself and my sister to talk more about it, and tell us that because of everything, that we might have to...make plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know my sister well enough to know she was just frozen in shock the same way I was. We both re-iterated about the seriousness from the end of the prior week, that we wanted to know about those kinds of things, and had to talk about the possibility of bereavement leave and similar in a weirdly matter-of-fact way. I just kinda felt like I was nodding along. I was already in the new job, but I'd only been in it for about a month. I don't know how I would've reacted if still with ShitPro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to see walf after. It's so hard to process in talking about it like that. I don't...I can't even remember everything I felt. It kinda felt like a blur after that that night. I didn't drink, I just...it's hard to remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, by the next morning, my mom texted us to say he was showing improvements! Throughout the week he slowly recovered more and more, and they were able to take him out of the medical coma, though I don't remember if it was under or over a week when they did. He slowly recovered, and the process of his lungs regaining strength was a long one for another couple weeks, working with doctors and my mom to try and regain oxygen carrying capabilities in his lungs. He's been through a fair amount of physical therapy, but after an issue the week before, he had go back to the hospital for a couple days because he caught COVID, again, and has pneumonia unrelated, again, but it's being treated. His initial pneumonia was also not from COVID at the time, but given he'd had it months prior and was coughing since then, I wondered if it was related. I even told my mom about ME/CFS at the time because I wondered if that's what he was suffering at the time of the intense period. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it's forward, slowly. He's on supplemental oxygen, and likely will be for the rest of his life. He's having a very hard time adjusting psychologically to the limitations his body has now. Maybe some he had for a while but could power through, but now he can't, and I know that's gotta be tremendously damaging for him. He I think turns 80 in April, and I think was imagining no problems til he was 90 even. I sure hoped so. I wanted to see things improve for him. But I don't know how much better they'll get, and doctors this past weekend told him if he has another major incident within a month or two, he should consider end-of-life care. Reading that was crushing to me. But I'm grateful I'll be able to see him at Christmas and still enough strength and warmth to greet me as he always has when I've gone home for Christmas. I'm tearing up writing this, because I don't know how many more that'll be, now, and that scares me. Despite the roughness and frustration I had growing up with him and his anger management issues, he was still always a very loving dad and very caring, and he loves seeing both my sister and I passionate about the things we enjoy, he loves hearing us talk about things we've learned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I can't imagine not having that anymore. Fuck, I was trying not to outright cry. Fuck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard to write now, but... that's a lot there. There's obviously tons I'm omitting. But I will try to be more active in writing this now that I've really made huge strides with this site. Domain might change, I dunno. I'm excited for a new refsheet at long last that really represents me! I'm learning more, building more, and most things are pretty good and empowering-feeling. I guess my dad's health was the trade-off for all that's going well. But if you made it this far, thank you for reading. I don't normally open up to this degree, and this has been a long difficult write for the past hour+. But I've wanted to share a lot of this in this level of detail, and now I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you all 🧡🎈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe I'll edit this later to break it up with things like Soatok x3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2023-12-14 11:27 AM CST: added context, dad had COVID.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"></category></entry><entry><title>Longer update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/longer-update.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/longer-update.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on to something infinitely less hateful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's funny, I wanted to update this because I've wanted to be able to make longer posts, but none really come to mind at-present. I'm just kinda out of it, tired, but I'm gonna have more uses soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Twitter exodus, I've been happy to host more folks on my Mastodon instance, and been thrilled to see the fediverse not only thriving but growing. It's a fantastic example of how decentralization really can be the future, just not the stupid shitcoin model every techbro has been trying to peddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Been doing a TON of baking over the past several years. I actually do want to make a post documenting all of this, but when I have more time and have had more sleep. I'd love to ramble like hell, and also write on the regular about my baking stuff. But for now, I think this'll do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"></category></entry><entry><title>Brief update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/brief-update.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/brief-update.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hi it's ass-oclock. My lovely boyfriend has been helping me fix my custom emoji plugin and I can once again build this site, yey! Very hopeful everything keeps going well. Brief update at least, but wanted to post SOMETHING to show this site isn't dead. Anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"></category></entry><entry><title>What Prompts Fursona Changes</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2020-08-06:/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT circulating Twitter&lt;/a&gt; about confessions that would make you "lose your furry card". Some of them are kinda stating the obvious, those "bold of you to state a common opinion" kind of things, not-so-hot/controversial takes (pedophilia is bad, don't fuck dogs, etc). I went to the original tweet just to peek at replies, and saw mentioned a couple times one that plagued me in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing your fursona is literally the most insane thing. "Oh, I'm not happy with the character I've made for myself, let me create another". That's in the DSM-V as a disability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is so much to unpack here that I can only say "holy shit". &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_frustrated" aria-label="kay_frustrated" title="kay_frustrated"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Comparing deciding to change your imaginary representation of yourself on the internet is not a disability holy fucking shit. I do think I know what causes this kind of hot take response, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until I actually went through one myself, I did not understand when people changed their fursonas. At first, at least. I did, a couple years prior to mine, finally start to understand that, yes, this is normal, it's not weird, it IS weird and shitty to be clingy to a previous sona. But having a sona change itself is fine. You're not obligated to keep the same imaginary avatar of yourself, and if anything, I think it's a good sign if it coincides with self-discovery in someone. You might realize that your avatar isn't really a good representation of you, or what you imagine your "best self" to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my case, I had thought dragon was, partly because I started in the dragonkin communities, and that tight tie to the idea of being otherkin kept me thinking I had to like it, I was supposed to, had to like dragons, etc etc. It was kind of exhausting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However once I separated from that kind of binding I better understood changes, better accepted others. I'd come up with kay in 2016, and by 2018 I'd changed over completely. When I "cut over", though, I started to receive that same sort of obsession: "Oh, but I liked Ceralor", or "but your dragon was hot I'm not hot for canines". It was like, what, do you think I'm gonna nix the character or the art? If I sold the character I'd sell the art with him, but I don't really think anyone's appropriate and the name's a handle for me anyway; it'd be hard to separate!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In keeping though, Ceralor stopped feeling representative of me, of "my best self", and he had been for some time, I realized, once I did decide to change. Canine had felt more accurate for some time, and the bouncy, wiggly, goofy nature felt far more at home for me upon picking it up more, it felt like me, actually me. I felt like I was free to really make Kay who I wanted him to be, to be my best self, instead of feeling constrained by expectations on a by-then-13-years-since-creation fursona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a lot of those negative reactions, a lot of people who felt like I wasn't the same person. In truth, I really wasn't perhaps the same how they expected, but at the same time I realized I really was the same person and just understood myself better now. And the compliments I got on Kay outweighed it, comments about how much better he fit me, how cute he was, silly, "real", it's hard to say, but it made me so happy and warm feeling! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway this was just a quick write-up thing because this was gonna be WAY too much text for Twitter. I'll try to keep this up-to-date more with posts!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2020"></category><category term="furry"></category><category term="fursona"></category></entry><entry><title>Camping dreams are weird</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-05-23:/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around for stuff on the trail, but as it got later, I ended up stopping for the night at a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good friend of mine who's big in pooltoys said "Yeah man, you can't beat the classics" in a voice I absolutely know I've heard him use IRL, but he was using it about a backpack that converted into a cot instead of a toy. I dunno why he was there, pfft. But it was still neat! Talked briefly to folks before going to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next morning my parents were somehow involved, and I was getting ready to pack up for the day, but apparently not hiking out yet, cause my sister and brother-in-law said something about messing up something on my car. Don't know why it was there. But then they were confused that we weren't yet leaving for the trail and would be spending the day in-town. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the day, I left to go buy supplies, but ended up buying lotto tickets. Turned around after buying them, and started wandering, only to find what looked like an entrance to a spacious Artist's Alley in a furry convention, and peeking in, I found a good friend of mine. Wandered over and said hey, and got a big warm hug, and I remember it making me super happy to see him, hee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird, but fun dream! I'd love more happy camping/backpacking/hiking dreams!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"></category><category term="camping"></category><category term="dreams"></category><category term="cons"></category></entry><entry><title>Fursona Sundries</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-04-19T07:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-19T22:39:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-04-19:/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play around with formatting a great deal but, hope folks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I'd like help with is a good way to format the miscellaneous information this page has!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/sundry.html"&gt;Check out the page here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class="accordions"&gt;
  &lt;article class="accordion"&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-header toggle"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Also playing with spoilers...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-body"&gt;
      &lt;div class="accordion-content"&gt;
        I've added a new bulma extension, for accordion support. Gonna use for spoilers. So much for no javascript, but CSS-based ones are a bit funky, maybe. We'll see!
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you can embed HTML in Markdown articles in pelican and it'll play nice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"></category><category term="furry"></category><category term="writing"></category></entry><entry><title>Returning to the guitar?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-01-27:/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved how the guitar sounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I've been thinking about it again. I'd first thought of snagging an electric guitar to learn on, but now I'm not certain I want to go that route. I miss the tone of an acoustic guitar, and I want to go that route. I decided to ask a friend who has been working on guitars for decades about it, and he's helping me out with picking out a starter, and encouraging it. And that's really helpful for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds silly I'm sure, but a part of this kinda inspired a comic idea, too, with Kay. But there's a little background and character detail I want to go over as well, to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay is really my fursona anymore. I'm silly and bouncy like he is, and get very giddy and giggly. But despite his toony, toyish nature, he's not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a toy. I think of 'toy' as more like an additional feature of him, not something that reduces or subtracts from him being a coyote. And I feel like that's kinda different as far as squeaksonas go. He has a normal job (like me), goes hiking and backpacking (like me), and loves music (like me). He can be happy and bouncy, or sad and morose, depressed even. Being a toy-type doesn't remove that at all. So that puts art involving him in an interesting place, trying to figure out or help an artist figure out in future ideas juxtaposing his slightly toony nature with perhaps more-serious situations. Which brings me to the comic idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: this goes into depression territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay, after his permanent transformation into a toy, possibly 'courtesy' of Coyote or some other deious entity, is a tremendous waterfall of feelings. Whilst he's always adored balloons and inflatables, being one, despite the excitement of it, is also terrifying. Though he's immune to most concerns of puncture and the like, there's the fears about being taken seriously anymore, about what others will think of him, about how he'll keep going in school and studies, and jobs later. Of what his parents would think. Even if he enjoys the form, he hates it (at first) as well. This has a huge toll on his psyche for canonically several days, maybe weeks. Even if he's enjoyed some inflationy fun with close friends, it still doesn't take his mind, ultimately, off of the "problem". &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going home the night after his TF, it's dark in his dorm when he arrives, wandering in with the lights off, and slumping onto his bed. He catches sight of his guitar and, after a moment of adjusting, finds he can still play, this wasn't taken from him. Playing slowly helps give him a little bit of a boost, to make him feel at least a little more like it's alright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damn. Writing it out like that... Maybe this doesn't need a comic. ~~Maybe this needs a short story, and a picture to go with it. Wonder what I can do in a thousand words. Doesn't seem like enough.~~ So I ended up writing out a short story of 1000 words, including articles, for it. May go back and update it to be 1000 words without articles, just to help it stand on its own better. &lt;a href="/files/Strings.pdf"&gt;It's right here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anywho, just a musing thinking about it. I'm excited to get back into this. I want to hear that sound again from my own fingers. I'm starting to take a bit of flight of my own in many ways, and this is just one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"></category><category term="music"></category><category term="learning"></category><category term="hobby"></category><category term="writing"></category></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, part deux!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-11-11:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span with 0.1px font size to hide the emoji name, also invisible color set, but still inside the &amp;lt;i&amp;gt; tag used to create the image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not perfect yet, I'd love for it to be more configurable, but it does its job for me for now, and mostly just requires manual work on my part in the theme to make sure the CSS file generated is accepted.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="emoji"></category><category term="mastodon"></category></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, Activate!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-25:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for &lt;code&gt;.png&lt;/code&gt; files, and then builds a list of those based on filename, so replacements are done using the filename minus the png, such as &amp;#58;kay_grinning&amp;#58; for the emoji in the opening! I'll try not to&lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-bike_pump" aria-label="bike_pump" title="bike_pump"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;this too much but it's very fun to have this working and usable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of the old replacer plugin for Pelican, functioning the same way but completely rewritten to make use of settings and building its own list for replacements to search for. The messy part is this requires scouring EVERY HTML file on write, but it works in the end. I'll have to find a nicer way to hook into this pre-write during the actual HTML-ization.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="emoji"></category><category term="mastodon"></category></entry><entry><title>Templates fuget</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-22:/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could do with having a visible sub-title for each type of index which will require fucking around with indexes a little more, and mapping specific templates to each index. Pelican does have some really neat flexibility, but the documentation is kind of poor. For instance, I had to explore to realize, hey, I can make a baseline no-content template that any fully-root pages can use (such as the home/index) and then make the actual &lt;code&gt;base.html&lt;/code&gt; (which it uses for all the other themes typically) extend this &lt;code&gt;prebase.html&lt;/code&gt; instead. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technicalities aside I really like what Pelican can do, and I want to see what I can do to push it further. I'd love to try and extend their documentation with better understanding, though their 'contributing' guide doesn't actually state anything about contributing to their somewhat lacking docs so...I guess I should just PR and find out how it goes? I guess @ me somewhere on input there! I've never really PR'd before to a public project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which...brings me to another question -- is it really worth it for me to host my own gitea instance at &lt;a class="link" href="https://coding.coyotesin.space"&gt;coding.coyotesin.space&lt;/a&gt; for my projects instead of github? I mean it's at least trivial to move something to Github -- make blank repo, add remote, &lt;code&gt;git push -u github&lt;/code&gt;, done. Dunno! Anywho, that's all I was thinking right now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="google"></category></entry><entry><title>Which office suite am I using?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-20:/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some Windows 2000 server, to using Exchange Server on a 2008 Small Biz server, and finally to using Google Apps for Biz. And this, my friends, is where the story begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I have to preface this story with something. Throughout using Google, the debit card he had attached frequently wouldn't have money in the specific account for it and couldn't pay the monthly bill. He'd ignore the billing messages until it was too late and service was suspended. Sometimes he'd put money on that card, sometimes he changed to a different card. But without fail, this issue would occur, regardless of the card. Seriously why do some boomers have so many debit cards what the fuck. There were like, 6 or 7 different banks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, every time the billing failed, I'd have to remind my dad we were paying Google to host his email. I'd have to play the exact same round of "20 Questions" to answer him, "yes we switched because your ISP wasn't reliable enough for Exchange", "no it's not running out of your office", "no this isn't free just because Gmail is free", "yes you still get emails from everyone". Every time it was the same questions. But let's move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two years ago and change, I'm realizing Google is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the right solution for my dad. The Outlook sync client would always break and he hated using the web UI for both Gmail and Google Calendar. The support for opening Word files in the online one sucked, and you can't open Gdoc files in Microsoft Office (you can but it's finicky to do). It simply was not what he needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point I proposed Office 365. I put together pricing, benefits, and presented it. He balked at the cost...and also forgot he was paying Google, again, for everything. I pushed a few times but never got the OK, so I let it be for a while...until his server started to have hardware issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He'd been storing files on his server for years and the age of the drives was showing. I'd never had an opportunity to rebuild his server from the ground up in order to properly get RAID going for redundancy on drives (was going to RAID1 three drives, because I knew I'd not hear about hardware failure until two had died). So I warned him of the dangers and told him we needed to move his files. I finally get the OK to move him to Microsoft. He'd balked in part at the cost because "I already have office", except it was a pirate copy (oops).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I get his email and calendar and contacts migrated without a hitch and Outlook reconfigured. Since it's 365, sync is flawless, everything Just Works and all seems to be right with the world. And this time, learning from my mistakes with Google, I'm handling billing myself. I knew I'd always have money on my account for it. I even start getting him going with OneDrive but...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Now instead of thinking it's self-hosted mail, he thinks it's with Google. It's like he's one step behind, constantly, on where things are. Now, he asks why I'm paying Microsoft for his mail. He says "But I thought we paid Google for that". Every time I re-explain my logic for the change. He also acknowledges the billing concern with why I took over it and refuse to relinquish the billing control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During vacation last weekend, my dad had some issues getting his tablet to talk to email. He forgot his password (again), so I logged in under my admin account and reset it for him and we got him signed in to his phone and tablet again. Fast forward to Wednesday, he's at home now and tells me Outlook isn't syncing. Now, I made the mistake of thinking he remembered to update his password (you see where this is going).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, more than that...he now told me Google was holding everything for ransom for $100 and thought Google was still using it. Turns out, he signed into his Google apps account in Chrome, and completely disregarded the password prompt in Outlook after what he thought was the password didn't work. I freak out, and finally get a chance to remote in. Plugged in his new password and all was well in Outlook, and I just signed him out of the defunct account in Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story: Google sucks massively.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"></category><category term="parents"></category><category term="support"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="msoffice"></category><category term="microsoft"></category><category term="google"></category></entry><entry><title>In which I don't imitate Garfield...</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-08:/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had a decent breakfast, bottled as it may be, and settling in for work included walking in to a systems down, which is what brings me to venting today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, my job role is a tier 3 role for systems administration at my company. But, with our company being acquired, and new infrastructure (read: internet and firewall) being installed, and with minimal training on it, I'm finding myself frustrated whenever I'm not able to get help from my coworker who knows the systems better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah well! I'm going to see if I can't figure out &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; means of installing a gallery type thing to this. I really like the idea of static sites, but if Pelican won't do I can look elsewhere I suppose. They're pretty similar all around, I presume.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"></category><category term="work"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="venting"></category></entry><entry><title>Starting Blog</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/starting-blog.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-07:/articles/2018/starting-blog.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon account whenever I post a new article, per like, RSS-feed updates. &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-ceralor_smile" aria-label="ceralor_smile" title="ceralor_smile"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Maybe. Or just manually.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog"></category><category term="furry"></category></entry></feed>