<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Coyotes in Space - blog</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/" rel="alternate"/><link href="https://coyotesin.space/feeds/blog.atom.xml" rel="self"/><id>https://coyotesin.space/</id><updated>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Cons are big</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/cons-are-big.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-03-07:/articles/2024/cons-are-big.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;And getting bigger. This is just a short post, but I'm struggling with the size of the cons expanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But even still, I find myself wanting to engage more and more with some of the events I pass on like dances and the like. I wanna have fun at those …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;And getting bigger. This is just a short post, but I'm struggling with the size of the cons expanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But even still, I find myself wanting to engage more and more with some of the events I pass on like dances and the like. I wanna have fun at those, and just...vibe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, my thoughts are much longer and this post'll get updated but I'm tired.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2024"/><category term="convention"/><category term="dance"/></entry><entry><title>Recovery</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/recovery.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-03-07T12:51:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-03-07:/articles/2024/recovery.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welp, sickness sucks. Emergencies suck more. Strap in, this one's definitely got some fun. 
Content Warnings: surgery, pain, medical, gross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So! Sunday evening, the 3rd, I started to feel a little bit of what I thought was just gas pain. I normally get it in my middle of my abdomen …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Welp, sickness sucks. Emergencies suck more. Strap in, this one's definitely got some fun. 
Content Warnings: surgery, pain, medical, gross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So! Sunday evening, the 3rd, I started to feel a little bit of what I thought was just gas pain. I normally get it in my middle of my abdomen, and it sucks, but it goes away eventually. This did not. It persisted, slowly getting worse. I kept farting here and there hoping that was relieving it, but it never truly did. I struggled with the bathroom, but it kept getting more persistent. It eventually started to spread outward, encompassing my lower right in it. By this point, it was probably 11 PM or later? I thought it might be appendicitis, but in that "WHAT IF IT WAS CANCER???" kind of way. Thank WebMD for fears like that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pain persisted and I kept trying to sleep, whimpering, tossing and turning as I kept shifting in the hopes it'd go away. Certain types of abdominal pressure helped, but overall it was just bad constantly. I finally fell asleep once I took Tylenol, which helped the pain subside some.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come Monday morning, I felt better, no more weird gas pain, but something else was there -- this weird nagging 'persistent' feeling in my left side. There was a presence there that insisted I know it was there, like using a highlighter on a word on white paper, but this was internal. I couldn't get rid of the nagging sensation. Nothing helped, and as the day wore on, lack of sleep kept me tired but feeling bad overall. Something was clearly wrong. I was talking to Mathias about it, who had asked about specifics the night before and wanted to keep an eye on specific feelings. He finally came over early afternoon to stay with me and help me feel better, but the sensation wouldn't go away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With both of us hoping it was something benign ultimately, some new sensation with IBS, we went to an urgent care clinic to check it out. There, they couldn't do much, a urinalysis, but overall nothing. But then the nurse practitioner came in, spoke to me, poked a little, and said I was presenting a lot of the classic signs of appendicitis -- pain and tenderness in the lower right, pressure, nausea, rebound pain when pushing on the left side of me, lower GI issues beyond IBS. It was probably serious, so she told me to go to an emergency department (ED/ER) and tell them the urgent clinic sent me with concerns of appendicitis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walf and I were still hoping that the imaging would rule it out -- I had no fever, no vomiting, no intense pain like people described with it being the worst pain they'd ever felt. But a CT scan showed the attending nurse practitioner (NP) at the ED that I almost certainly had acute appendicitis, and an hour later radiology concurred. The main hospital would set me up a room, and I would ride in an ambulance for the first, and hopefully last, time. (BUMPY!) I was told I'd almost certainly be operated on by a surgeon the NP had perform on him once, which was a pretty glowing review to me! I was also comforted by hearing that it'd also likely be laparoscopic, minimally-invasive -- just 3-4 little tiny incisions on the belly to operate and that's it! (Spoiler alert: this did not happen.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They couldn't schedule me for surgery that night, so they transported me to the main hospital, and up to my room there, allowing Mathias to spend the night there with me and helping him get some bedding in the room with me. I was in pain, but treated with morphine that helped the pain considerably at low dosage, only 2mg at a time -- 4mg gave this TERRIBLE rush sensation up the back of my shoulders and neck that I &lt;strong&gt;hated&lt;/strong&gt; feeling. I don't get why people like it. But the low dosage helped, and I slept, intermittently because of repeated waking, but I still slept.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a side note, the nurse at this time, at the hospital, had some indirect connections, apparently having worked at the same Panera a good local friend of ours works at, and her fiance having worked for the same computer repair place I worked at after I left it. Small world! She was SUPER nice and helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waking, I met that doctor I was told about, who told me he'd be making sure he could do the minimally-invasive and then I'd be feeling better soon. Much more pain today, but again, managed through drugs. But soon after, I met a different doctor, who said &lt;em&gt;he'd&lt;/em&gt; be doing my surgery instead, and that he would &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; do the laparoscopic -- not because he didn't know how or wasn't good at it, but because he didn't "like" it. "But then you have 3-4 incisions and scars instead of just one!" I think I'd have preferred that over what I have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever. He reassured both Mathias and I and so I was promptly prepped for surgery, taken down to pre-op, where the din of the place and the sounds, the treatment, the disorganization (four &lt;strong&gt;different&lt;/strong&gt; people asked me the same questions!) had me quickly skyrocketing in anxiety, and Mathias thankfully was back there and with me because I broke into tears at some point. He also gave me my earplugs, but well before I was given the drug to start to go under general anesthesia, a nurse told me I had to take them out, which sucked because they were helping me manage my anxiety. I was scared, and upset, but the lady shaving my belly for surgery helped me calm a fair bit. Pain, but she was comforting with talking a little as she did, and taking her time. At some point I was given a large dose of ondansetron for upcoming nausea and then an anti-anxiety drug that had me calming down, everything feeling melty, and promptly passing out without even realizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next thing I knew, just like with tooth surgery, I was in considerable pain and they were trying to help with things in post-op, getting stuff worked out, talking about room transfers as if I'd end up in a different room than I'd been in. But finally they decided the same room I'd been in, and I was transported -- feeling every. Fucking. Bump. The most minor bumps, the acceleration of a rotation even gentle, starting or stopping and ESPECIALLY those GOD DAMN ELEVATOR BUMPS felt like HELL on where I'd been operated on. I could barely move, I was trying not to cry, just tired and stressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then they picked me up, sheet and all, and put me in my bed again. And my pain spiked so high I yelped as it shot up past a 10 for me there, and I promptly broke down sobbing as they left -- feeling tired, afraid, hurting, abandoned by them, cared &lt;em&gt;at&lt;/em&gt; instead of &lt;em&gt;for&lt;/em&gt; and just... terrible. Upset and angry my want for laparoscopic had been overturned because some old doctor didn't "like" it. Who fucking cares if it takes longer, I'm unconcious, what the shit do I care? It felt like he was just trying to speedrun surgery instead of &lt;strong&gt;patient&lt;/strong&gt; care being the focus, and just reminded me so much of how many people feel this way in the US's current medical treatment pipeline. I just wanted everything to feel better -- even remembering now I'm choking a little because of how bad it felt. But Mathias was there for me, and held my hand and what he could safely do of me and kissed my head, staying close as I cried with the pain and hurt of it. I had no option here, I had to get surgery immediately or I would've died, I had no chance to pick a doctor or facility, I was stuck with whatever I had. Every jingoistic asshole talking about how "Americans have choice in healthcare though" compared to other systems can fuck RIGHT the hell off, they've clearly never had emergency care needs because I don't get to fucking pick, I just have to hope wherever I end up is covered by my insurance or that I can fight with my insurance for it. I'm grateful that my insurance will likely make this expensive, but still something I can afford, though I don't feel like it's right for me to have to pay $800-1000 just because some part of my body decided to fuck up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pain meds helped, and some water, some rest, and I started to feel a little better. I felt well enough to eat the dinner I was served in full, and in full I did -- I was starving at this point, Tuesday evening, since I'd had nothing to eat since Monday early afternoon. I rested in and out a fair bit, woken repeatedly for vitals and the like. I had to repeatedly watch for air in the line because people were inattentive too, I pointed out a large one to a nurse in training just before she injected some into me, and had to withdraw it which pulled blood into the IV line, oh well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Wednesday morning I just wanted to go. I wanted things over. I wanted pain to stop, I wanted everything normal, but I couldn't. My gut was starting to try to move again, but couldn't, and as I was getting released, I started to get gas pain again, but this time it was very clearly just gas pain moving around the small intestines and into the large one. But finally I was discharged after the nurse's attitude changed some I think seeing how stressed and upset I was from everything. There seemed to be constant miscommunication, or misunderstanding, and the nurse pointed out that's all it was but...that doesn't change how I as a patient feel in that situation. It sucked. Again, I felt cared &lt;em&gt;at&lt;/em&gt; rather chan cared &lt;em&gt;for&lt;/em&gt; and I couldn't really word it any other way. The act of caring without directly caring for me individually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, I worked through it, nurse helped me with walking some more, good advice, and I was given medication to drop my blood pressure from being so high and then released. Also at this point I had a LOT of gas discomfort and bubbling and I was trying badly to fart, so bad that the first time I did I almost moaned with relief. It felt like the best fart ever because holy hell, you don't realize what it feels like when that whole system just STOPS and then needs to start again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm writing this while at my desk, while Mathias is in the living room working at my work desk, staying with me. Immensely grateful for him being here. I told my boss I'll be out this week and be back WFH on Monday, though may be WFH that week. I'll recover. It'll take some time, but I'll be back to normal again soon I hope.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2024"/><category term="hospital"/><category term="surgery"/><category term="pain"/></entry><entry><title>Winter-time End-of-year wishes</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/winter-time-end-of-year-wishes.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2023-12-24T16:25:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-24T16:25:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-12-24:/articles/2023/winter-time-end-of-year-wishes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;With many friends of many faiths, and especially myself not being religious, I don't quite feel right wishing anyone a "Merry Christmas", nor a "happy holidays", as I don't want to seem like I'm co-opting a holy month of the year for many. But I still want to share &lt;em&gt;something …&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;With many friends of many faiths, and especially myself not being religious, I don't quite feel right wishing anyone a "Merry Christmas", nor a "happy holidays", as I don't want to seem like I'm co-opting a holy month of the year for many. But I still want to share &lt;em&gt;something.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winter's always been a fairly special time for me less for holidays as holy days, but more the season being unique-feeling, snow, time with family, visits, and sharing love with people I care about. Presents were always nice as a kid of course, but I don't think about them much now. I'm just appreciative of things at any time of year, and so Christmas-time is more of "winter holiday" for me. It's why I also want to do cookies in January, because I want to give people cheer where I can, something nice. Seasonal affective sucks, and if I can help others having it any and combat my own in the process, all the better! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just want everyone to have a wonderful winter time, especially if spent with family, and if they're in need of some form of cheer, that they can find it, whether through born family, chosen family, friends, or even strangers. Take time for you during these darker Northern months, or warmer Southern months, wherever you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Big squeaky hugs from a puffy coyote who just wants to spread a few smiles if he can. 🧡🎈&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"/><category term="christmas"/><category term="holidays"/><category term="winter"/></entry><entry><title>New Job, Budding Hobbies, and Family Health</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2023-12-13T14:30:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-14T11:27:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-12-13:/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh god was this long to prep. I started writing this with the intent of it just being a blog update, and then got into getting Mastodon comments into this blog, fixing styling issues, fixing imports and dependencies so I could just use npm to install things...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...it was a …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh god was this long to prep. I started writing this with the intent of it just being a blog update, and then got into getting Mastodon comments into this blog, fixing styling issues, fixing imports and dependencies so I could just use npm to install things...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...it was a lot. Shit. I've nearly forgotten what I was gonna write. At least the subject's still staring at me, so...there's that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fair warning in advance, this post will contain talk about outsiders and family having critical health conditions as well as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll start off as it says in order, new job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="new-job"&gt;New Job&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="but-we-gotta-start-with-the-old"&gt;but we gotta start with the old&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id="so-first-up-where-i-was-and-why-it-sucked"&gt;so first up, where I was and why it sucked&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting at the end of 2012, all the way up through mid-July of this year, I'd worked for the same company more-or-less -- shifting roles, company acquisitions, etc. I started in call center and eventually ended up a systems administrator for a healthcare software company, AKA, an independent medical review org, part of the reason why insurance sucks so much in the US. I'll refer to them as ShitPro in this post, it's vaguely like their name. For a long time I'd convinced myself that this role was OK, because most of ShitPro's clients were Medicaid (government-funded healthcare per-state, for those outside the US). The idea was that it was "saving them money" by "figuring out if doctors really tried everything they needed for patients", except a lot of times patients had to do the lifting with doctors to let them know drugs couldn't be filled, because doctors didn't think that their licensed practice of medicine would be second-guessed by a bunch of suits, rightfully so, and thus had not started a PA to begin with. I didn't fully understand it at first, but once I did, I think I convinced myself it was fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to early 2021, early 2022? I don't remember. In either case, I ended up, now a systems admin and handling technology that was used for all of ShitPro's clients (including &lt;strong&gt;private&lt;/strong&gt; health insurance now, ugh) fielding a request about a fax. The provider (doctor or hospital) in question blamed ShitPro for bungling an appeal for halting a hospital discharge. I'm not sure how that's something Medicare (federal-gov-paid healthcare) can do, but they apparently can, or something. Either way, I reviewed the case in question and found the fax &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; sent to ShitPro before the like, 2:30 PM or 3:00 PM deadline -- I dunno exactly, these deadlines are based on when the case is opened, not a specific time of day, it's fucked up. But it was only &lt;em&gt;started&lt;/em&gt; before that deadline, not completed, and because it's all digital, and faxes are a physically-analog process even when transmitted between digital services, the fax didn't complete for nearly 2 hours, pushing it an hour &lt;em&gt;past&lt;/em&gt; that deadline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was livid. I was talking to a coworker on a voice call who was able to help me track down with what she could see in her application, and she had a verbal shrug, because both of our hands were tied. I tried to reply back to the person entering the case, and they just cared "did ShitPro receive the fax file late due to no fault of ShitPro?" and unfortunately, the answer was a technical yes because the FTP server was fine, nothing had slowed it down other than the time it takes for a fax to transfer. Hell, if it was still paper, I bet they would've had the same fucking response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was more upset, it started sinking in how people were being affected. My walf was facing issues with PAs as well, through the other half of who ShitPro formerly was, split off in a merger, and I felt responsible &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; helpless at the same time. I wanted to make it right, I wanted to make things work, but I had no power to poke anyone who could do anything of consequence, and my role in contributing to the operation of these platforms, even without being the one making the decisions, started weighing very heavily on me. But I wasn't making enough to just leave or find something lower income to immediately switch to because of other financial obligations. So I sulked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A month later after the fax incident, I had a new ticket. "ManagerName is getting voicemails she's not supposed to get from emailsender". I reached out and had a sample email forwarded. Because these voicemails were to digital systems that transcribed, I was unable to avoid seeing the contents in trying to troubleshoot. It was too close to the areas I needed to look at. Even without playing the attachment I felt like I could hear the helpless voice of a woman trying desperately to keep getting her mother the hospital care she and doctors felt were needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even now this hurts to remember. I was crushed. I couldn't work the rest of the week. I was work-from-home, so no one could see me sitting on the couch all day instead. But the night of that I cried, sobbed in my walf's arms in a park I'd met up with him at to just get outside, get some fresh air at night. It was cold and I felt like the shittiest person on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I slowly managed to pull something together, but from then on, every day at my job for the next I dunno, year and a half, two years? Every day felt interminable. Every so often some task would come up that would snag that ADHD interest, that burned at the right synapses to engage me, but it wasn't often. I started hunting for a new job, but I barely had the energy to try, and unlike many of my friends, I don't have a specialized knowledge set. My knowledge in technology is very broad, with deeper areas in some places, but nothing like I felt like most places demanded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="the-job-hunt-begins-slowly"&gt;the job hunt begins, slowly&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I met up with a former coworker, who also hated ShitPro for similar reasons, for a beer to talk about what his employer had available after learning about the roles. I was interested, and applied, but it turned out to be a dead end lead. My former coworker tried to find other ways to get me in, but they'd all require I take a pay cut first for an unknown amount of time before I could be moved to the team he was in. I passed, and started looking again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then a furry friend offered to refer me for the same team he was on, same position, at Indeed. It sounded fantastic on paper -- integrating employer talent programs and applicant tracking systems with Indeed's systems in a multitude of ways to make it easier for people to apply for jobs and for employers to review applications. It sounded great. And based on what the recruiter told me, I was the only other one when they selected someone else for the 'lead' role, after almost 10 interviews, due to lack of leadership experience. But I was told to apply again when a senior-level position opened. I kept tuned and attentive, and applied when I finally got notice it was open. I was ecstatic still, and the new recruiter called me and told me he was astounded they hadn't picked me last time based on the feedback he read from everyone who interviewed me. He wasn't sure what all they'd need to do since it was only a few months later, but promised a very high likelihood I'd net it just because of that. But 2 days later I got a call again, informing me that unfortunately the position was removed, no one accepted in, and Indeed was going on a hiring freeze for an unknown amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stuck again, I didn't really know what to do. I kept looking around here and there when I found energy. The success with Indeed had weirdly empowered me slightly, and started to make me angry at ShitPro, and want to find something better. Finally, I ended up looking at jobs at the university here, Auburn. I found several job positions I could do, though many I didn't want to do anymore (was exhausted with sysadmin work). But there were a few that piqued my interest, and I applied. Vordex, another local fur and fellow coyote, who works there, told me not to expect to hear back from them for a while, because his A/V role got a callback months later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="and-finally-forward-motion"&gt;And finally forward motion&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got an email the next week, while at FWA 2023. They wanted to interview for a position that I was genuinely interested in, and I was very excited. That fast despite what I was told? I was really eager, and so were they, interviewing me literally less than a week later!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a great interview. I felt really good about things, I was unsure of myself in a few spaces due to lack of experience, but the courteousness with which everyone greeted me and talked to me gave me confidence that I could do what was needed, I could learn whatever I was missing to fill in those empty spots. I think 1-2 weeks later I got an email back asking for an in-person interview on campus, setting up to meet more people. I went in, sat down, and felt really nervous but good in talking to people. I was even asked if, because I don't have a degree, if I'd planned to use Auburn's free hours each semester to take classes while employed. I had no idea they had it, and said I'd absolutely do so because that was exciting too! I never finished, and I wanted to go back and try again, this time in an MIS role instead of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And about a week later I got a call from my new manager telling me that if I accepted the verbal offer, I'd be sent a written one to sign to become a university employee. I about cried in joy at this. I felt like shackles were breaking free that I'd been trapped with for so long I'd forgotten they were there. As soon as I signed the written offer with a start date, I put in my notice with ShitPro, and anxiety built with a need to &lt;em&gt;leave&lt;/em&gt; that place for good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="and-the-new-job-at-last"&gt;And the new job at last&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The folks who interviewed me ended up being pretty direct coworkers. One sits next to me, and I'm working with him closely on building out a new campus portal that's replacing the aging old one. The hiring manager is my direct manager, a guy who does much more work than management because he trusts the people under him, he works with us, and is a generally great guy. The 'exec' who'd asked about the tuition benefit is my boss's manager, also a very nice guy who's friendly each time he sees me. So many folks here know my name just from meeting in a good way early on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And even with a very slow start building over a few months, I feel useful. I feel wanted, needed here, not out of desperation, but because of valuing me. I'm doing work that makes student lives easier and helps faculty and staff as well. It feels almost like a penance for working for ShitPro for so long, but a penance I'm grateful for the opportunity to perform, and enjoying as well. The university's even queer-friendly as hell; there've been &lt;strong&gt;massive&lt;/strong&gt; diversity and inclusion improvements across all facets since I'd last known what the university had to offer. Once a month on a Friday I go with Vordex to have coffee with a bunch of other queer coworkers on campus, and it's fantastic. Sometimes it feels like a dream it's been so huge of an improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="remember-that-tuition-benefit"&gt;Remember that tuition benefit?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auburn offers employees of at least a year of service up to 5 hours of courses each semester paid by the university. Given my role, I had to be granted a student role in the application, allowing me to see that there was still an academic hold on my account preventing registration. I'd not been sure what to do, but about 2 weeks ago at queer coffee I heard the director of the pride center talking to someone about care she'd been giving in academic management to students who had trouble with it. Speaking up, I asked if she knew about academic holds, and she said she did, and figured what I was going to ask. I showed her the hold, and she asked for details. As I started to talk at first, I found I could pull up my unofficial transcript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the entire... 14 years? It was Spring 2007 when I left. In the whole time, I'd never looked at my grades for that second and final semester I had there until sitting there on campus again with someone who could help. And looking at a column of nothing but F's except for my men's chorus course welled up all those painful feelings I had buried for so long. I choked a little, but showed her. As we talked, I started to choke up more when she started talking to me about ways to address it. She said it'd be easy to work past, as long as I could maintain a per-semester average.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, given it was so bad for that one semester, she had another idea: retroactive medical discharge. My mental health was in the toilet that year, and I couldn't even bear going to classes most of the time. The combination of welling old pain, and a new sense of hope that I could erase that entire mark on my record and start as if it'd never happened? I don't know how I avoided sobbing from the mixture, I definitely wasn't able to hold back tears. She told me she would help me with the case, needing a letter from me to explain the need for medical discharge. So that's my next task for that, is work on that, to try and undo some of the pain of the past and start fresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that's where I am. You can see a little bit how all of this contributes to that feeling of it nearly being a dream, hah! I'm excited, I'm eager, and I have a drive to wipe out that pain and start anew on something I can better handle. And I want to take the classes, I want to learn more. I can even take them during work hours, why wouldn't I take that benefit? I'm really eager and excited now. 🧡&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="budding-hobbies"&gt;Budding Hobbies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that that's out of the way, besides baking a lot more and having fun, I started getting more into 3D. This is probably gonna be a pretty short section by comparison ahaha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple months ago I started up a Blender course I was gifted. I'd never taken a course, and my previous attempts with Blender had been with that donut tutorial, which I couldn't reproduce for the life of me. It felt like I wasn't capable of learning as a result, but it turns out that tutorial just blows. Turns out &lt;a href="https://www.gamedev.tv"&gt;GameDev.TV&lt;/a&gt; have some fantastic instructors who don't act like they're some whizbang rockstar teaching you to be the same. I'm still working through the course, but he built fundamentals first, navigation, basic tools, and started into editing, starting out with an island and lighthouse. From there, it was on to building a modular dungeon with reusable parts, learning some more-advanced tooling for warping things slightly, for adjustments, cuts, mirroring, learning enough to start figuring out how to make low-polygon shapes and models. It's been incredible to learn! I genuinely feel like I'm getting a better sense of using Blender, and have already begun making minor changes to things, and even modeled myself a low-poly puffy crown to use in VR Chat!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've never been able to draw because of my dyspraxia, and while I know there's plenty of artists with it who make due, and do wonderful art, it's only ever been a frustration for me. Finally learning in a visual art that isn't impaired by that because of using tooling for changes has been phenomenal. I feel excited as I learn more, I've been able to actually take advantage of what I've learned like I said, and I feel like, with enough practice and learning, that I could eventually make custom models entirely like what folks see, and that REALLY excites me to be able to do! So, I'm continuing to push forward with glee for that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="family-health"&gt;Family Health&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Figured that'd be a short section. So, family health really concerns only one person: my dad. And again, this gets medically-graphic, fair warning. No one dies but there &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; mention of death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months ago, I got a message from my mom on a Thursday talking about the weather, and then as &lt;strong&gt;nearly&lt;/strong&gt; an aside at the end, telling us (my sister and I) that dad was in the hospital, but don't worry! Both of us replied in shock, hospital is a big deal for a stay, why didn't she tell us? "Well your dad didn't want you to worry and didn't think it was a big deal." Chat, I think you can imagine what came next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By that Friday night, my mom texted us to say that the doctors were keeping him because his pneumonia was so bad, and his O2 was so low, that they had to intubate him. He was put into a medically-induced coma to let his lungs recover. But over the weekend, each day the news was worse and worse. That Monday morning my mom texted us to say that the doctors weren't sure why he wasn't responding to medications, but were going to give him steroids, as... a "last ditch effort". I like to hope it was not that dire. I don't know the reality, and likely never will. And I'm kinda glad for that. But that night, my mom voice-called myself and my sister to talk more about it, and tell us that because of everything, that we might have to...make plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know my sister well enough to know she was just frozen in shock the same way I was. We both re-iterated about the seriousness from the end of the prior week, that we wanted to know about those kinds of things, and had to talk about the possibility of bereavement leave and similar in a weirdly matter-of-fact way. I just kinda felt like I was nodding along. I was already in the new job, but I'd only been in it for about a month. I don't know how I would've reacted if still with ShitPro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had to see walf after. It's so hard to process in talking about it like that. I don't...I can't even remember everything I felt. It kinda felt like a blur after that that night. I didn't drink, I just...it's hard to remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, by the next morning, my mom texted us to say he was showing improvements! Throughout the week he slowly recovered more and more, and they were able to take him out of the medical coma, though I don't remember if it was under or over a week when they did. He slowly recovered, and the process of his lungs regaining strength was a long one for another couple weeks, working with doctors and my mom to try and regain oxygen carrying capabilities in his lungs. He's been through a fair amount of physical therapy, but after an issue the week before, he had go back to the hospital for a couple days because he caught COVID, again, and has pneumonia unrelated, again, but it's being treated. His initial pneumonia was also not from COVID at the time, but given he'd had it months prior and was coughing since then, I wondered if it was related. I even told my mom about ME/CFS at the time because I wondered if that's what he was suffering at the time of the intense period. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it's forward, slowly. He's on supplemental oxygen, and likely will be for the rest of his life. He's having a very hard time adjusting psychologically to the limitations his body has now. Maybe some he had for a while but could power through, but now he can't, and I know that's gotta be tremendously damaging for him. He I think turns 80 in April, and I think was imagining no problems til he was 90 even. I sure hoped so. I wanted to see things improve for him. But I don't know how much better they'll get, and doctors this past weekend told him if he has another major incident within a month or two, he should consider end-of-life care. Reading that was crushing to me. But I'm grateful I'll be able to see him at Christmas and still enough strength and warmth to greet me as he always has when I've gone home for Christmas. I'm tearing up writing this, because I don't know how many more that'll be, now, and that scares me. Despite the roughness and frustration I had growing up with him and his anger management issues, he was still always a very loving dad and very caring, and he loves seeing both my sister and I passionate about the things we enjoy, he loves hearing us talk about things we've learned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I can't imagine not having that anymore. Fuck, I was trying not to outright cry. Fuck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="summary"&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard to write now, but... that's a lot there. There's obviously tons I'm omitting. But I will try to be more active in writing this now that I've really made huge strides with this site. Domain might change, I dunno. I'm excited for a new refsheet at long last that really represents me! I'm learning more, building more, and most things are pretty good and empowering-feeling. I guess my dad's health was the trade-off for all that's going well. But if you made it this far, thank you for reading. I don't normally open up to this degree, and this has been a long difficult write for the past hour+. But I've wanted to share a lot of this in this level of detail, and now I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you all 🧡🎈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe I'll edit this later to break it up with things like Soatok x3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EDIT 2023-12-14 11:27 AM CST: added context, dad had COVID.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"/></entry><entry><title>Longer update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/longer-update.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/longer-update.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on to something infinitely less hateful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's funny, I wanted to update this because I've wanted to be able to make longer posts, but none really come to mind at-present. I'm just kinda out of it, tired, but I'm gonna have more uses soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Twitter exodus, I've been happy to host more folks on my Mastodon instance, and been thrilled to see the fediverse not only thriving but growing. It's a fantastic example of how decentralization really can be the future, just not the stupid shitcoin model every techbro has been trying to peddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Been doing a TON of baking over the past several years. I actually do want to make a post documenting all of this, but when I have more time and have had more sleep. I'd love to ramble like hell, and also write on the regular about my baking stuff. But for now, I think this'll do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"/></entry><entry><title>Brief update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/brief-update.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/brief-update.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hi it's ass-oclock. My lovely boyfriend has been helping me fix my custom emoji plugin and I can once again build this site, yey! Very hopeful everything keeps going well. Brief update at least, but wanted to post SOMETHING to show this site isn't dead. Anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2023"/></entry><entry><title>What Prompts Fursona Changes</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2020-08-06:/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT circulating Twitter&lt;/a&gt; about confessions that would make you "lose your furry card". Some of them are kinda stating the obvious, those "bold of you to state a common opinion" kind of things, not-so-hot/controversial takes (pedophilia is bad, don't fuck dogs, etc). I went to the original tweet just to peek at replies, and saw mentioned a couple times one that plagued me in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing your fursona is literally the most insane thing. "Oh, I'm not happy with the character I've made for myself, let me create another". That's in the DSM-V as a disability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is so much to unpack here that I can only say "holy shit". &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_frustrated" aria-label="kay_frustrated" title="kay_frustrated"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Comparing deciding to change your imaginary representation of yourself on the internet is not a disability holy fucking shit. I do think I know what causes this kind of hot take response, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until I actually went through one myself, I did not understand when people changed their fursonas. At first, at least. I did, a couple years prior to mine, finally start to understand that, yes, this is normal, it's not weird, it IS weird and shitty to be clingy to a previous sona. But having a sona change itself is fine. You're not obligated to keep the same imaginary avatar of yourself, and if anything, I think it's a good sign if it coincides with self-discovery in someone. You might realize that your avatar isn't really a good representation of you, or what you imagine your "best self" to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my case, I had thought dragon was, partly because I started in the dragonkin communities, and that tight tie to the idea of being otherkin kept me thinking I had to like it, I was supposed to, had to like dragons, etc etc. It was kind of exhausting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However once I separated from that kind of binding I better understood changes, better accepted others. I'd come up with kay in 2016, and by 2018 I'd changed over completely. When I "cut over", though, I started to receive that same sort of obsession: "Oh, but I liked Ceralor", or "but your dragon was hot I'm not hot for canines". It was like, what, do you think I'm gonna nix the character or the art? If I sold the character I'd sell the art with him, but I don't really think anyone's appropriate and the name's a handle for me anyway; it'd be hard to separate!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In keeping though, Ceralor stopped feeling representative of me, of "my best self", and he had been for some time, I realized, once I did decide to change. Canine had felt more accurate for some time, and the bouncy, wiggly, goofy nature felt far more at home for me upon picking it up more, it felt like me, actually me. I felt like I was free to really make Kay who I wanted him to be, to be my best self, instead of feeling constrained by expectations on a by-then-13-years-since-creation fursona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a lot of those negative reactions, a lot of people who felt like I wasn't the same person. In truth, I really wasn't perhaps the same how they expected, but at the same time I realized I really was the same person and just understood myself better now. And the compliments I got on Kay outweighed it, comments about how much better he fit me, how cute he was, silly, "real", it's hard to say, but it made me so happy and warm feeling! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway this was just a quick write-up thing because this was gonna be WAY too much text for Twitter. I'll try to keep this up-to-date more with posts!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2020"/><category term="furry"/><category term="fursona"/></entry><entry><title>Camping dreams are weird</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-05-23:/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around for stuff on the trail, but as it got later, I ended up stopping for the night at a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good friend of mine who's big in pooltoys said "Yeah man, you can't beat the classics" in a voice I absolutely know I've heard him use IRL, but he was using it about a backpack that converted into a cot instead of a toy. I dunno why he was there, pfft. But it was still neat! Talked briefly to folks before going to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next morning my parents were somehow involved, and I was getting ready to pack up for the day, but apparently not hiking out yet, cause my sister and brother-in-law said something about messing up something on my car. Don't know why it was there. But then they were confused that we weren't yet leaving for the trail and would be spending the day in-town. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the day, I left to go buy supplies, but ended up buying lotto tickets. Turned around after buying them, and started wandering, only to find what looked like an entrance to a spacious Artist's Alley in a furry convention, and peeking in, I found a good friend of mine. Wandered over and said hey, and got a big warm hug, and I remember it making me super happy to see him, hee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird, but fun dream! I'd love more happy camping/backpacking/hiking dreams!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="camping"/><category term="dreams"/><category term="cons"/></entry><entry><title>Fursona Sundries</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-04-19T07:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-19T22:39:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-04-19:/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play around with formatting a great deal but, hope folks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I'd like help with is a good way to format the miscellaneous information this page has!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/sundry.html"&gt;Check out the page here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class="accordions"&gt;
  &lt;article class="accordion"&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-header toggle"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Also playing with spoilers...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-body"&gt;
      &lt;div class="accordion-content"&gt;
        I've added a new bulma extension, for accordion support. Gonna use for spoilers. So much for no javascript, but CSS-based ones are a bit funky, maybe. We'll see!
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you can embed HTML in Markdown articles in pelican and it'll play nice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="furry"/><category term="writing"/></entry><entry><title>Returning to the guitar?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-01-27:/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved how the guitar sounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I've been thinking about it again. I'd first thought of snagging an electric guitar to learn on, but now I'm not certain I want to go that route. I miss the tone of an acoustic guitar, and I want to go that route. I decided to ask a friend who has been working on guitars for decades about it, and he's helping me out with picking out a starter, and encouraging it. And that's really helpful for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds silly I'm sure, but a part of this kinda inspired a comic idea, too, with Kay. But there's a little background and character detail I want to go over as well, to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay is really my fursona anymore. I'm silly and bouncy like he is, and get very giddy and giggly. But despite his toony, toyish nature, he's not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a toy. I think of 'toy' as more like an additional feature of him, not something that reduces or subtracts from him being a coyote. And I feel like that's kinda different as far as squeaksonas go. He has a normal job (like me), goes hiking and backpacking (like me), and loves music (like me). He can be happy and bouncy, or sad and morose, depressed even. Being a toy-type doesn't remove that at all. So that puts art involving him in an interesting place, trying to figure out or help an artist figure out in future ideas juxtaposing his slightly toony nature with perhaps more-serious situations. Which brings me to the comic idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: this goes into depression territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay, after his permanent transformation into a toy, possibly 'courtesy' of Coyote or some other deious entity, is a tremendous waterfall of feelings. Whilst he's always adored balloons and inflatables, being one, despite the excitement of it, is also terrifying. Though he's immune to most concerns of puncture and the like, there's the fears about being taken seriously anymore, about what others will think of him, about how he'll keep going in school and studies, and jobs later. Of what his parents would think. Even if he enjoys the form, he hates it (at first) as well. This has a huge toll on his psyche for canonically several days, maybe weeks. Even if he's enjoyed some inflationy fun with close friends, it still doesn't take his mind, ultimately, off of the "problem". &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going home the night after his TF, it's dark in his dorm when he arrives, wandering in with the lights off, and slumping onto his bed. He catches sight of his guitar and, after a moment of adjusting, finds he can still play, this wasn't taken from him. Playing slowly helps give him a little bit of a boost, to make him feel at least a little more like it's alright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damn. Writing it out like that... Maybe this doesn't need a comic. ~~Maybe this needs a short story, and a picture to go with it. Wonder what I can do in a thousand words. Doesn't seem like enough.~~ So I ended up writing out a short story of 1000 words, including articles, for it. May go back and update it to be 1000 words without articles, just to help it stand on its own better. &lt;a href="/files/Strings.pdf"&gt;It's right here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anywho, just a musing thinking about it. I'm excited to get back into this. I want to hear that sound again from my own fingers. I'm starting to take a bit of flight of my own in many ways, and this is just one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2019"/><category term="music"/><category term="learning"/><category term="hobby"/><category term="writing"/></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, part deux!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-11-11:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span with 0.1px font size to hide the emoji name, also invisible color set, but still inside the &amp;lt;i&amp;gt; tag used to create the image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not perfect yet, I'd love for it to be more configurable, but it does its job for me for now, and mostly just requires manual work on my part in the theme to make sure the CSS file generated is accepted.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"/><category term="website"/><category term="tech"/><category term="emoji"/><category term="mastodon"/></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, Activate!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-25:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for &lt;code&gt;.png&lt;/code&gt; files, and then builds a list of those based on filename, so replacements are done using the filename minus the png, such as &amp;#58;kay_grinning&amp;#58; for the emoji in the opening! I'll try not to&lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-bike_pump" aria-label="bike_pump" title="bike_pump"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;this too much but it's very fun to have this working and usable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of the old replacer plugin for Pelican, functioning the same way but completely rewritten to make use of settings and building its own list for replacements to search for. The messy part is this requires scouring EVERY HTML file on write, but it works in the end. I'll have to find a nicer way to hook into this pre-write during the actual HTML-ization.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"/><category term="website"/><category term="tech"/><category term="emoji"/><category term="mastodon"/></entry><entry><title>Templates fuget</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-22:/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could do with having a visible sub-title for each type of index which will require fucking around with indexes a little more, and mapping specific templates to each index. Pelican does have some really neat flexibility, but the documentation is kind of poor. For instance, I had to explore to realize, hey, I can make a baseline no-content template that any fully-root pages can use (such as the home/index) and then make the actual &lt;code&gt;base.html&lt;/code&gt; (which it uses for all the other themes typically) extend this &lt;code&gt;prebase.html&lt;/code&gt; instead. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technicalities aside I really like what Pelican can do, and I want to see what I can do to push it further. I'd love to try and extend their documentation with better understanding, though their 'contributing' guide doesn't actually state anything about contributing to their somewhat lacking docs so...I guess I should just PR and find out how it goes? I guess @ me somewhere on input there! I've never really PR'd before to a public project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which...brings me to another question -- is it really worth it for me to host my own gitea instance at &lt;a class="link" href="https://coding.coyotesin.space"&gt;coding.coyotesin.space&lt;/a&gt; for my projects instead of github? I mean it's at least trivial to move something to Github -- make blank repo, add remote, &lt;code&gt;git push -u github&lt;/code&gt;, done. Dunno! Anywho, that's all I was thinking right now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"/><category term="website"/><category term="tech"/><category term="google"/></entry><entry><title>Which office suite am I using?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-20:/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some Windows 2000 server, to using Exchange Server on a 2008 Small Biz server, and finally to using Google Apps for Biz. And this, my friends, is where the story begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I have to preface this story with something. Throughout using Google, the debit card he had attached frequently wouldn't have money in the specific account for it and couldn't pay the monthly bill. He'd ignore the billing messages until it was too late and service was suspended. Sometimes he'd put money on that card, sometimes he changed to a different card. But without fail, this issue would occur, regardless of the card. Seriously why do some boomers have so many debit cards what the fuck. There were like, 6 or 7 different banks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, every time the billing failed, I'd have to remind my dad we were paying Google to host his email. I'd have to play the exact same round of "20 Questions" to answer him, "yes we switched because your ISP wasn't reliable enough for Exchange", "no it's not running out of your office", "no this isn't free just because Gmail is free", "yes you still get emails from everyone". Every time it was the same questions. But let's move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two years ago and change, I'm realizing Google is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the right solution for my dad. The Outlook sync client would always break and he hated using the web UI for both Gmail and Google Calendar. The support for opening Word files in the online one sucked, and you can't open Gdoc files in Microsoft Office (you can but it's finicky to do). It simply was not what he needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point I proposed Office 365. I put together pricing, benefits, and presented it. He balked at the cost...and also forgot he was paying Google, again, for everything. I pushed a few times but never got the OK, so I let it be for a while...until his server started to have hardware issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He'd been storing files on his server for years and the age of the drives was showing. I'd never had an opportunity to rebuild his server from the ground up in order to properly get RAID going for redundancy on drives (was going to RAID1 three drives, because I knew I'd not hear about hardware failure until two had died). So I warned him of the dangers and told him we needed to move his files. I finally get the OK to move him to Microsoft. He'd balked in part at the cost because "I already have office", except it was a pirate copy (oops).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I get his email and calendar and contacts migrated without a hitch and Outlook reconfigured. Since it's 365, sync is flawless, everything Just Works and all seems to be right with the world. And this time, learning from my mistakes with Google, I'm handling billing myself. I knew I'd always have money on my account for it. I even start getting him going with OneDrive but...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Now instead of thinking it's self-hosted mail, he thinks it's with Google. It's like he's one step behind, constantly, on where things are. Now, he asks why I'm paying Microsoft for his mail. He says "But I thought we paid Google for that". Every time I re-explain my logic for the change. He also acknowledges the billing concern with why I took over it and refuse to relinquish the billing control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During vacation last weekend, my dad had some issues getting his tablet to talk to email. He forgot his password (again), so I logged in under my admin account and reset it for him and we got him signed in to his phone and tablet again. Fast forward to Wednesday, he's at home now and tells me Outlook isn't syncing. Now, I made the mistake of thinking he remembered to update his password (you see where this is going).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, more than that...he now told me Google was holding everything for ransom for $100 and thought Google was still using it. Turns out, he signed into his Google apps account in Chrome, and completely disregarded the password prompt in Outlook after what he thought was the password didn't work. I freak out, and finally get a chance to remote in. Plugged in his new password and all was well in Outlook, and I just signed him out of the defunct account in Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story: Google sucks massively.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"/><category term="parents"/><category term="support"/><category term="tech"/><category term="msoffice"/><category term="microsoft"/><category term="google"/></entry><entry><title>In which I don't imitate Garfield...</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-08:/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had a decent breakfast, bottled as it may be, and settling in for work included walking in to a systems down, which is what brings me to venting today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, my job role is a tier 3 role for systems administration at my company. But, with our company being acquired, and new infrastructure (read: internet and firewall) being installed, and with minimal training on it, I'm finding myself frustrated whenever I'm not able to get help from my coworker who knows the systems better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah well! I'm going to see if I can't figure out &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; means of installing a gallery type thing to this. I really like the idea of static sites, but if Pelican won't do I can look elsewhere I suppose. They're pretty similar all around, I presume.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog/2018"/><category term="work"/><category term="website"/><category term="tech"/><category term="venting"/></entry><entry><title>Starting Blog</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/starting-blog.html" rel="alternate"/><published>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-07:/articles/2018/starting-blog.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon account whenever I post a new article, per like, RSS-feed updates. &lt;i class="pelimoji pelimoji-ceralor_smile" aria-label="ceralor_smile" title="ceralor_smile"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Maybe. Or just manually.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="blog"/><category term="furry"/></entry></feed>