<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Coyotes in Space - General</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://coyotesin.space/feeds/general.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://coyotesin.space/</id><updated>2023-12-13T14:30:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>New Job, Budding Hobbies, and Family Health</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-13T14:30:00-06:00</published><updated>2023-12-13T14:30:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-12-13:/articles/2023/new-job-budding-hobbies-and-family-health.html</id><content type="html"></content><category term="General"></category></entry><entry><title>Longer update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/longer-update.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/longer-update.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Because it's been so long since my last post on here, it's...been quite a lot I've gone through over the past 3 years. I've been working from home, moved, fell in love with a wonderful walf, and now am leaving my job of 10.5 years to move on to something infinitely less hateful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's funny, I wanted to update this because I've wanted to be able to make longer posts, but none really come to mind at-present. I'm just kinda out of it, tired, but I'm gonna have more uses soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the Twitter exodus, I've been happy to host more folks on my Mastodon instance, and been thrilled to see the fediverse not only thriving but growing. It's a fantastic example of how decentralization really can be the future, just not the stupid shitcoin model every techbro has been trying to peddle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Been doing a TON of baking over the past several years. I actually do want to make a post documenting all of this, but when I have more time and have had more sleep. I'd love to ramble like hell, and also write on the regular about my baking stuff. But for now, I think this'll do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category></entry><entry><title>Brief update</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2023/brief-update.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-06-06T02:03:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2023-06-06:/articles/2023/brief-update.html</id><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hi it's ass-oclock. My lovely boyfriend has been helping me fix my custom emoji plugin and I can once again build this site, yey! Very hopeful everything keeps going well. Brief update at least, but wanted to post SOMETHING to show this site isn't dead. Anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category></entry><entry><title>What Prompts Fursona Changes</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-08-06T16:40:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2020-08-06:/articles/2020/what-prompts-fursona-changes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT …&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is kind of a weird post as a hello again to my site, but after seeing a take that rubbed me very much the wrong way, in part because I've seen it many times since 2016, I wanted to write up: Fursona Changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now there's a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GiganticPaws/status/1291091420716003333"&gt;meme-type quote-RT circulating Twitter&lt;/a&gt; about confessions that would make you "lose your furry card". Some of them are kinda stating the obvious, those "bold of you to state a common opinion" kind of things, not-so-hot/controversial takes (pedophilia is bad, don't fuck dogs, etc). I went to the original tweet just to peek at replies, and saw mentioned a couple times one that plagued me in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changing your fursona is literally the most insane thing. "Oh, I'm not happy with the character I've made for myself, let me create another". That's in the DSM-V as a disability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is so much to unpack here that I can only say "holy shit". &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-kay_frustrated" aria-label="kay_frustrated" title="kay_frustrated"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Comparing deciding to change your imaginary representation of yourself on the internet is not a disability holy fucking shit. I do think I know what causes this kind of hot take response, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until I actually went through one myself, I did not understand when people changed their fursonas. At first, at least. I did, a couple years prior to mine, finally start to understand that, yes, this is normal, it's not weird, it IS weird and shitty to be clingy to a previous sona. But having a sona change itself is fine. You're not obligated to keep the same imaginary avatar of yourself, and if anything, I think it's a good sign if it coincides with self-discovery in someone. You might realize that your avatar isn't really a good representation of you, or what you imagine your "best self" to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my case, I had thought dragon was, partly because I started in the dragonkin communities, and that tight tie to the idea of being otherkin kept me thinking I had to like it, I was supposed to, had to like dragons, etc etc. It was kind of exhausting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However once I separated from that kind of binding I better understood changes, better accepted others. I'd come up with kay in 2016, and by 2018 I'd changed over completely. When I "cut over", though, I started to receive that same sort of obsession: "Oh, but I liked Ceralor", or "but your dragon was hot I'm not hot for canines". It was like, what, do you think I'm gonna nix the character or the art? If I sold the character I'd sell the art with him, but I don't really think anyone's appropriate and the name's a handle for me anyway; it'd be hard to separate!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In keeping though, Ceralor stopped feeling representative of me, of "my best self", and he had been for some time, I realized, once I did decide to change. Canine had felt more accurate for some time, and the bouncy, wiggly, goofy nature felt far more at home for me upon picking it up more, it felt like me, actually me. I felt like I was free to really make Kay who I wanted him to be, to be my best self, instead of feeling constrained by expectations on a by-then-13-years-since-creation fursona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a lot of those negative reactions, a lot of people who felt like I wasn't the same person. In truth, I really wasn't perhaps the same how they expected, but at the same time I realized I really was the same person and just understood myself better now. And the compliments I got on Kay outweighed it, comments about how much better he fit me, how cute he was, silly, "real", it's hard to say, but it made me so happy and warm feeling! &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway this was just a quick write-up thing because this was gonna be WAY too much text for Twitter. I'll try to keep this up-to-date more with posts!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="furry"></category><category term="fursona"></category></entry><entry><title>Camping dreams are weird</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-05-23T07:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-05-23:/articles/2019/camping-dreams-are-weird.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dreams are so weird sometimes. And fun! I had a dream last night that somehow evolved into hearing that it was too late for hikers to start on the northbound (NOBO) hike of the Appalachian Trail. And I was hiking it apparently, along with some friends. I remember looking around for stuff on the trail, but as it got later, I ended up stopping for the night at a shelter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good friend of mine who's big in pooltoys said "Yeah man, you can't beat the classics" in a voice I absolutely know I've heard him use IRL, but he was using it about a backpack that converted into a cot instead of a toy. I dunno why he was there, pfft. But it was still neat! Talked briefly to folks before going to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next morning my parents were somehow involved, and I was getting ready to pack up for the day, but apparently not hiking out yet, cause my sister and brother-in-law said something about messing up something on my car. Don't know why it was there. But then they were confused that we weren't yet leaving for the trail and would be spending the day in-town. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of the day, I left to go buy supplies, but ended up buying lotto tickets. Turned around after buying them, and started wandering, only to find what looked like an entrance to a spacious Artist's Alley in a furry convention, and peeking in, I found a good friend of mine. Wandered over and said hey, and got a big warm hug, and I remember it making me super happy to see him, hee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weird, but fun dream! I'd love more happy camping/backpacking/hiking dreams!&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="camping"></category><category term="dreams"></category><category term="cons"></category></entry><entry><title>Fursona Sundries</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-04-19T07:18:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-19T22:39:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-04-19:/articles/2019/fursona-sundries.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;An unusual post this time! I've been thinking about the background for Kay, both as a fursona and a character, and figured that there's a LOT of attributes a regular refsheet type thing wouldn't cover. So, I'm putting together a page for it here on the site! I'll probably play around with formatting a great deal but, hope folks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing that I'd like help with is a good way to format the miscellaneous information this page has!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/sundry.html"&gt;Check out the page here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;section class="accordions"&gt;
  &lt;article class="accordion"&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-header toggle"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Also playing with spoilers...&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class="accordion-body"&gt;
      &lt;div class="accordion-content"&gt;
        I've added a new bulma extension, for accordion support. Gonna use for spoilers. So much for no javascript, but CSS-based ones are a bit funky, maybe. We'll see!
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/article&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm glad you can embed HTML in Markdown articles in pelican and it'll play nice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="furry"></category><category term="writing"></category></entry><entry><title>Returning to the guitar?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</published><updated>2019-01-27T22:47:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2019-01-27:/articles/2019/returning-to-the-guitar.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, I took up casual guitar lessons using my mom's classical guitar. At the time I was young and more comitted to going through motions of prep than the practice itself. I never really took the time to learn well, eventually stopped the lessons. But I always loved how the guitar sounded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I've been thinking about it again. I'd first thought of snagging an electric guitar to learn on, but now I'm not certain I want to go that route. I miss the tone of an acoustic guitar, and I want to go that route. I decided to ask a friend who has been working on guitars for decades about it, and he's helping me out with picking out a starter, and encouraging it. And that's really helpful for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds silly I'm sure, but a part of this kinda inspired a comic idea, too, with Kay. But there's a little background and character detail I want to go over as well, to help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay is really my fursona anymore. I'm silly and bouncy like he is, and get very giddy and giggly. But despite his toony, toyish nature, he's not &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a toy. I think of 'toy' as more like an additional feature of him, not something that reduces or subtracts from him being a coyote. And I feel like that's kinda different as far as squeaksonas go. He has a normal job (like me), goes hiking and backpacking (like me), and loves music (like me). He can be happy and bouncy, or sad and morose, depressed even. Being a toy-type doesn't remove that at all. So that puts art involving him in an interesting place, trying to figure out or help an artist figure out in future ideas juxtaposing his slightly toony nature with perhaps more-serious situations. Which brings me to the comic idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: this goes into depression territory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kay, after his permanent transformation into a toy, possibly 'courtesy' of Coyote or some other deious entity, is a tremendous waterfall of feelings. Whilst he's always adored balloons and inflatables, being one, despite the excitement of it, is also terrifying. Though he's immune to most concerns of puncture and the like, there's the fears about being taken seriously anymore, about what others will think of him, about how he'll keep going in school and studies, and jobs later. Of what his parents would think. Even if he enjoys the form, he hates it (at first) as well. This has a huge toll on his psyche for canonically several days, maybe weeks. Even if he's enjoyed some inflationy fun with close friends, it still doesn't take his mind, ultimately, off of the "problem". &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going home the night after his TF, it's dark in his dorm when he arrives, wandering in with the lights off, and slumping onto his bed. He catches sight of his guitar and, after a moment of adjusting, finds he can still play, this wasn't taken from him. Playing slowly helps give him a little bit of a boost, to make him feel at least a little more like it's alright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damn. Writing it out like that... Maybe this doesn't need a comic. ~~Maybe this needs a short story, and a picture to go with it. Wonder what I can do in a thousand words. Doesn't seem like enough.~~ So I ended up writing out a short story of 1000 words, including articles, for it. May go back and update it to be 1000 words without articles, just to help it stand on its own better. &lt;a href="/files/Strings.pdf"&gt;It's right here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anywho, just a musing thinking about it. I'm excited to get back into this. I want to hear that sound again from my own fingers. I'm starting to take a bit of flight of my own in many ways, and this is just one of them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="music"></category><category term="learning"></category><category term="hobby"></category><category term="writing"></category></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, part deux!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T15:24:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-11-11:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-part-deux.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;More updates on the project! &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-thumbs_up_paw" aria-label="thumbs_up_paw" title="thumbs_up_paw"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This site now has more &lt;a href="https://mutant.tech"&gt;Mutant Standard&lt;/a&gt; emoji in use, and now uses a &lt;a href="/emoji_map/emoji.png"&gt;spritesheet&lt;/a&gt; for the emoji, after some help from &lt;a href="https://jaesond.cc"&gt;Jaeson&lt;/a&gt;. This also allows me to be far more screenreader-friendly, accessibility oriented, not relying on images and alt text, instead using a span with 0.1px font size to hide the emoji name, also invisible color set, but still inside the &amp;lt;i&amp;gt; tag used to create the image.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not perfect yet, I'd love for it to be more configurable, but it does its job for me for now, and mostly just requires manual work on my part in the theme to make sure the CSS file generated is accepted.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="emoji"></category><category term="mastodon"></category></entry><entry><title>Custom Emoji, Activate!</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-25T23:14:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-25:/articles/2018/custom-emoji-activate.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh hey, I just wanted to say, custom emoji work! &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-kay_grinning" aria-label="kay_grinning" title="kay_grinning"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; I call it Pelimoji, a plugin for Pelican to allow simple replacement of colon-called emoji stored in a pre-defined directory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of Mastodon's CSS implementation using emojione. The script implementing this scours a setting directory for &lt;code&gt;.png&lt;/code&gt; files, and then builds a list of those based on filename, so replacements are done using the filename minus the png, such as &amp;#58;kay_grinning&amp;#58; for the emoji in the opening! I'll try not to&lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-bike_pump" aria-label="bike_pump" title="bike_pump"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;this too much but it's very fun to have this working and usable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is based roughly off of the old replacer plugin for Pelican, functioning the same way but completely rewritten to make use of settings and building its own list for replacements to search for. The messy part is this requires scouring EVERY HTML file on write, but it works in the end. I'll have to find a nicer way to hook into this pre-write during the actual HTML-ization.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="emoji"></category><category term="mastodon"></category></entry><entry><title>Templates fuget</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-22T16:43:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-22:/articles/2018/templates-fuget.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Been meaning to make this site really look a lot nicer, so I've been faffing around with things and I think I've finally got the beginnings of something! I still need to theme &lt;a href="/tags.html" class="link"&gt;the tags page&lt;/a&gt; to look nicer, but the indexes look OK so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I could do with having a visible sub-title for each type of index which will require fucking around with indexes a little more, and mapping specific templates to each index. Pelican does have some really neat flexibility, but the documentation is kind of poor. For instance, I had to explore to realize, hey, I can make a baseline no-content template that any fully-root pages can use (such as the home/index) and then make the actual &lt;code&gt;base.html&lt;/code&gt; (which it uses for all the other themes typically) extend this &lt;code&gt;prebase.html&lt;/code&gt; instead. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technicalities aside I really like what Pelican can do, and I want to see what I can do to push it further. I'd love to try and extend their documentation with better understanding, though their 'contributing' guide doesn't actually state anything about contributing to their somewhat lacking docs so...I guess I should just PR and find out how it goes? I guess @ me somewhere on input there! I've never really PR'd before to a public project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which...brings me to another question -- is it really worth it for me to host my own gitea instance at &lt;a class="link" href="https://coding.coyotesin.space"&gt;coding.coyotesin.space&lt;/a&gt; for my projects instead of github? I mean it's at least trivial to move something to Github -- make blank repo, add remote, &lt;code&gt;git push -u github&lt;/code&gt;, done. Dunno! Anywho, that's all I was thinking right now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="google"></category></entry><entry><title>Which office suite am I using?</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-20T16:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-20:/articles/2018/which-office-suite-am-i-using.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been handling computer support for my dad for the better part of the last 15 years, give and take some times when he's had someone else working on it. I've helped him grow from using a local ISP's email, to using self-hosted email with his own domain on some Windows 2000 server, to using Exchange Server on a 2008 Small Biz server, and finally to using Google Apps for Biz. And this, my friends, is where the story begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I have to preface this story with something. Throughout using Google, the debit card he had attached frequently wouldn't have money in the specific account for it and couldn't pay the monthly bill. He'd ignore the billing messages until it was too late and service was suspended. Sometimes he'd put money on that card, sometimes he changed to a different card. But without fail, this issue would occur, regardless of the card. Seriously why do some boomers have so many debit cards what the fuck. There were like, 6 or 7 different banks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, every time the billing failed, I'd have to remind my dad we were paying Google to host his email. I'd have to play the exact same round of "20 Questions" to answer him, "yes we switched because your ISP wasn't reliable enough for Exchange", "no it's not running out of your office", "no this isn't free just because Gmail is free", "yes you still get emails from everyone". Every time it was the same questions. But let's move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two years ago and change, I'm realizing Google is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; the right solution for my dad. The Outlook sync client would always break and he hated using the web UI for both Gmail and Google Calendar. The support for opening Word files in the online one sucked, and you can't open Gdoc files in Microsoft Office (you can but it's finicky to do). It simply was not what he needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point I proposed Office 365. I put together pricing, benefits, and presented it. He balked at the cost...and also forgot he was paying Google, again, for everything. I pushed a few times but never got the OK, so I let it be for a while...until his server started to have hardware issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He'd been storing files on his server for years and the age of the drives was showing. I'd never had an opportunity to rebuild his server from the ground up in order to properly get RAID going for redundancy on drives (was going to RAID1 three drives, because I knew I'd not hear about hardware failure until two had died). So I warned him of the dangers and told him we needed to move his files. I finally get the OK to move him to Microsoft. He'd balked in part at the cost because "I already have office", except it was a pirate copy (oops).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I get his email and calendar and contacts migrated without a hitch and Outlook reconfigured. Since it's 365, sync is flawless, everything Just Works and all seems to be right with the world. And this time, learning from my mistakes with Google, I'm handling billing myself. I knew I'd always have money on my account for it. I even start getting him going with OneDrive but...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Now instead of thinking it's self-hosted mail, he thinks it's with Google. It's like he's one step behind, constantly, on where things are. Now, he asks why I'm paying Microsoft for his mail. He says "But I thought we paid Google for that". Every time I re-explain my logic for the change. He also acknowledges the billing concern with why I took over it and refuse to relinquish the billing control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During vacation last weekend, my dad had some issues getting his tablet to talk to email. He forgot his password (again), so I logged in under my admin account and reset it for him and we got him signed in to his phone and tablet again. Fast forward to Wednesday, he's at home now and tells me Outlook isn't syncing. Now, I made the mistake of thinking he remembered to update his password (you see where this is going).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, more than that...he now told me Google was holding everything for ransom for $100 and thought Google was still using it. Turns out, he signed into his Google apps account in Chrome, and completely disregarded the password prompt in Outlook after what he thought was the password didn't work. I freak out, and finally get a chance to remote in. Plugged in his new password and all was well in Outlook, and I just signed him out of the defunct account in Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moral of the story: Google sucks massively.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="parents"></category><category term="support"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="msoffice"></category><category term="microsoft"></category><category term="google"></category></entry><entry><title>In which I don't imitate Garfield...</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-08T09:51:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-08:/articles/2018/in-which-i-dont-imitate-garfield.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good morning. Or bad. Or meh! I dunno. It's a morning at least, and one in which plans don't seem to matter, so horray for that I guess? Buh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Was hoping to go for a walk this morning but my earlier alarm never went off, so oops! At least had a decent breakfast, bottled as it may be, and settling in for work included walking in to a systems down, which is what brings me to venting today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, my job role is a tier 3 role for systems administration at my company. But, with our company being acquired, and new infrastructure (read: internet and firewall) being installed, and with minimal training on it, I'm finding myself frustrated whenever I'm not able to get help from my coworker who knows the systems better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah well! I'm going to see if I can't figure out &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; means of installing a gallery type thing to this. I really like the idea of static sites, but if Pelican won't do I can look elsewhere I suppose. They're pretty similar all around, I presume.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="work"></category><category term="website"></category><category term="tech"></category><category term="venting"></category></entry><entry><title>Starting Blog</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2018/starting-blog.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-10-07T14:30:00-05:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2018-10-07:/articles/2018/starting-blog.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Oh, hey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I should start up a simple blog thing here as part of my site, heh! I've been wanting to make a nice simple site more than just my &lt;a class="link" href="https://coyotesin.space"&gt;regular homepage&lt;/a&gt;, so here we are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm also going to see if I can't autopost to my Blimpstodon account whenever I post a new article, per like, RSS-feed updates. &lt;i class="cemoji cemoji-ceralor_smile" aria-label="ceralor_smile" title="ceralor_smile"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Maybe. Or just manually.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="General"></category><category term="furry"></category></entry></feed>