<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Coyotes in Space - Story/One for the Road</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://coyotesin.space/feeds/story/one-for-the-road.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://coyotesin.space/</id><updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated><entry><title>Sleeper</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/sleeper.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/sleeper.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cody tried not to keep staring at the ferret as he worked. A second night was promised if he absolutely had to, but with the clerk’s shift only starting 2 hours ago, the coyote wasn’t sure he could keep awake that long. He continued staring out the window …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Cody tried not to keep staring at the ferret as he worked. A second night was promised if he absolutely had to, but with the clerk’s shift only starting 2 hours ago, the coyote wasn’t sure he could keep awake that long. He continued staring out the window into the blizzard. The same sight as the night before, hardly changed. Even during the day, it hardly seemed to get light out, between the latitude and blizzard raging outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody stood for a moment, and took a sip of the coffee Thomas gave him a few minutes prior. A nice perk, and he’d seen the ferret let a few kinder folks with refill mugs leave if all they got was coffee. “Why bother?” he’d told the coyote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He walked over to the door, taking a step out into the blustery cold. The fur of his nap bristled and fluffed, but he only felt the cold seep in after a moment standing there. “To think my ancestors probably just curled up in the snow in weather like this,” Cody mused with a dry chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thoughts swirled in his mind as he looked towards the black clouds above. Abandoned. Ejected. Hated. He looked down into his coffee, as if for something else. No words came.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘Selfish.’ ‘After all he did for you.’&lt;/em&gt; The coyote practically stumbled back, leaning against the wall. “Stop it…” he whispered to the empty lot before him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What made you think this would be different? What made you think this would work out?’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because I loved him,” the coyote choked, his throat tight. “Stop…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘You loved the idea of him. You loved the idea of being cared about, of being important to someone, why would—’&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I SAID FUCKING STOP!” Cody shouted, as salty ice formed below his eyes. “Fucking fuck off!” His voice didn’t even echo in the snow, as the thoughts quieted, leaving him panting, and shaking. “Fuck,” he said, much more quietly, wiping his face on his coat with a sniff before turning back inside. Away from the cold. Away from even colder thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Cody stepped back inside and wiped his shoes on the carpet, splaying his toes to get the snow out from under them as well, he caught a whiff of a new scent. Or not so much new as new-in-context. He returned to his backpack, sniffing around it briefly, and then down at himself. Nothing. Maybe Thomas took a cue from him to ‘stealth’ today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody shrugged it off, settling back down to sit again, and look out into the snow, letting the din of truckers coming and going roll past as he focused on the falling flakes, as they danced and wheeled about. “Maybe I could just get a job here?” he mused to himself. It was peaceful enough. The truckers had been friendly. It was a nice change from what he’d seen where he grew up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“...Cody…”, Thomas said, perking up the coyote’s ears. As they swiveled for a fix, the bustle settled into a few distinct voices. He couldn’t clearly focus on the ferret anymore, but he knew he’d heard his name amongst the various sounds, a few new ones blending into the mix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before turning his head to see what the ferret was up to, the scent of rubber graced his nose once more. And in caution again, he sniffed at himself, downward, then towards his backpack. Nothing. Only a faint hit, not the warmer one. Not the strength he picked up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ah, you Cody?” spoke an unfamiliar voice, and as the coyote turned his head to his addresser, his eyes widened. The question of the scent was immediately answered. The timberwolf before Cody stood easily half-again the coyote’s height, if not more, a trucker given the vague stereotype of a white t-shirt covered by an unbuttoned plaid flannel shirt with the sleeves rolled up partly, and jeans. All of which seemed like they were moments from clinging to the timberwolf for dear life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the biggest attention grabber for the eyes was in what &lt;em&gt;wasn’t&lt;/em&gt; covered by the clothing; a smooth, soft gloss took the place of the normal fur of his hands, forearms, face, and even a bit peeking out from under the shirt. Was that…?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Er, y’alright there? Hope I didn’t uh, interrupt somethin’,” the wolf spoke softly. As his stance shifted, it elicited a faint ‘sqrk’, similar to the sounds during the cuddling session the night before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I...yeah, that’s me, sorry, um...who did you say your na-I mean, what did...yeah,” the coyote stumbled out before looking up to greet the wolf’s soft expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hah, I ain’t yet. ‘Name’s Brandon,” he replied, extending one of those thick handpaws to shake, which nearly swallowed Cody’s. &lt;em&gt;Rubber. It really is. Warm, soft rubber, not...solid?&lt;/em&gt; “Thomas over there said yuh were in a bit-of-a bind n'… well, I’ve known him a good while, n’ trust him t’ only point out someone ah can trust.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trust…? Thomas...me?” Cody asked. Words were hard at the moment as his brain tried critically to process the sight before him, and kept ending up in places that would embarrass him and nearly sent his face into a beet-red blush. But he kept it in check.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Heh, he didn’t think ya’d drink much o’ that coffee yet, guess he was right,” the wolf replied with a chuckle, as he walked around the row of chairs to take a seat in the empty one to Cody’s side. The heady scent of latex was absolutely unmistakable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody kept silent for a moment as he followed Brandon’s steps, looking briefly down to catch sight of his paws in a similar open-foot shoe to the coyote’s, letting the glossy sheen of the paws and toes show, exposed as they were. “What’re…” he started, before shaking his head, and looking back up to Brandon. “Sorry, I uh…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timberwolf laughed, giving the coyote’s upper back a pat with one of those thick, glossy paws. “I get it, don’t worry yerself there; Thomas s’like that when ah first met him too. S’what you think exactly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody thought he might faint at the thought. “You’re really…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Rubber, latex ah guess, n’ air, yeah. But uh, that aside fer the moment,” Brandon started. He struggled for words, before beginning. “Look, ah know I ain’t the smoothest when it comes t’ greetin’ folks fer somethin’ like this, usually that's just my hide, but I’ve got a proposition. My hauls are pretty long, n’ with how dark it gets this time of year, the drives are pretty borin’ n’ quiet. So, in exchange fer some company on the drives, yer free t’ ride along with me. No other ulterior motives, I promise. Tired o’ drivin’ alone, n’ I’d rather help a friendly fellah out than just anyone. Yer free to leave at any time – at least if we’re somewhere safe, ain’t about t’ letcha get off if we’re just somewhere in the middle of the woods...not that ah can really stop yuh but...y’know, wouldn’t be right o’ me to not try,” the wolf said, rubbing the back of his head lightly with a chuckle at the last bit, eliciting a few more rubbery squirks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody sat listening, his eyes slightly wide, but with a lightly tired laze he tried to push back. “You...want me to ride with you? On your truck?” he asked, only barely realizing he was just repeating the wolf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, basically. Ain’t gotta do anythin’ on the truck, unless yer handy n’ wanna if somethin’ happens. Look, I know this is a lot at once, so I ain’t gonna be surprised or upset if y’ say ‘no’. But I know how much it sucks t’ feel abandoned, n’ if I can help in some way and it gives me a lil company too…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“...Most folks I guess think you’re...well...this isn’t what &lt;em&gt;I&lt;/em&gt; think but, ‘weird’?” Cody asked, wincing slightly as he realized how awkward that sounded. Not the fastest tonight, he thought, and took a sip of his coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yyyeah, guess so. N’ ah figured you wouldn’t, cause...well, wolves have a pretty good sense of smell, even like this,” Brandon replied. Cody’s toes curled slightly as his mask failed. No hiding that blush. “Besides, Thomas wouldn’t point me your way if he thought you’d be put off. And it’s...well, nice, fer stuff t’ be the opposite of that,” the wolf added, his own cheeks a touch pink as he spoke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That...fuck it. That sounds like a change of pace I need," Cody said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What’re you doing?’&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been wanting to see more of the Northern lands,” the coyote added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;‘What’re you doing this’ll never work!’&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And I...I don’t know what I’ve been waiting for, here,” Cody replied, swallowing as he did his best to ignore those thoughts. “Maybe this, this kinda thing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brandon smiled, and let out a cheerful laugh. It was a warm sound, slightly reverberant, in a way that cemented the wolf’s description. Rubber and air. “What, some kinda adventure? Heh, can’t really say it’d be an adventure of a typical sort, but…” he extended his paw to shake again. “We’ll figure out anything as we go.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody took that giant handpaw in both of his own, both to squeeze and lightly rub to confirm for himself a third time that his eyes weren’t deceiving him. Warm, soft, squeaky, squishy. “Uh...then, yeah, I guess so. As long as I won’t be in the way.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Not a bit. Grab what you need, and meet me at my truck out back. We’re gonna drive a bit further on t’night, it’s pretty early still, for me at least,” the wolf asked, holding up his own coffee. A gallon mug. The coyote figured he’d ask later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody nodded, and felt a smile cross his muzzle for only the second time yet at the truck stop. “Yeah,” he replied, with another squeeze to the wolf’s paw before he released it, nodding again as Brandon stood, striding off towards the back of the store towards the trucker exit. As the wolf left, the coyote stood as well, letting out a deep sigh as residual tension left him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’s got a heart of gold. I wouldn’t have pointed him toward you if I didn’t trust him,” came Thomas’s voice, causing the coyote to quickly turn to face the attendant. “Sorry, I guess you were too focused to hear me walk up. But I mean it,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where the hell did you even meet him?” the coyote asked, his voice quieter than usual. “What even…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He stopped in one night while I was working, and just kinda...hit it off well. He’s stopped in many times over the past couple years to say howdy and for a hug,” the ferret replied, rubbing the back of his own head with a slight sheepish expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You mean he smelled you stealthing and realized you’d be friendly?” the coyote teased. He felt lighter, easier, more at-ease than he had. “I’m teasing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“And right,” Thomas laughed, shaking his head. “I know he’ll take good care of you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote stood, and after a brief pause, embraced Thomas in a tight hug the ferret returned. “Thank you. You’ve been incredibly sweet.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can thank me by giving me another hug like that in a week; should be back by here then,” the ferret replied, releasing the hug and patting Cody’s sides. “Now grab a fresh hot coffee, and some food on me, and get on the road.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry><entry><title>Stranded</title><link href="https://coyotesin.space/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/stranded.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2024-01-02T00:00:00-06:00</updated><author><name>Kay Ohtie</name></author><id>tag:coyotesin.space,2024-01-02:/articles/2024/story/one-for-the-road/stranded.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Sir?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody grunted softly, stirred from a doze. He blinked several times, looking around blearily, realizing he’d dozed off. He took in his surroundings, seated in a sitting area near the food court of the truck stop. Looking out the large pane window before him, the same site he …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“Sir?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody grunted softly, stirred from a doze. He blinked several times, looking around blearily, realizing he’d dozed off. He took in his surroundings, seated in a sitting area near the food court of the truck stop. Looking out the large pane window before him, the same site he’d seen a few hours ago greeted him: a black night sky and a furious blizzard’s clumps and flakes billowing past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sir? I’m sorry, sir, but you can’t sleep here,” came the voice again, belonging to a small ferret, a clerk, the coyote surmised, based on the name tag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blinking away the remaining daze, he simply nodded. “Yeah uhm… sorry. I didn’t mean to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret smiled, chuckling. “I can tell. Here,” he replied as held up one of the stop’s paper mugs towards the sleepy canine. “My manager won’t try to get me to kick you out as long as you’re awake. I’m sorry we don’t have any spare bunks right now, with the blizzard.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote nodded, a weak smile flashed in return. The ferret was cute, he thought to himself, as he quietly accepted the mug, taking a long sip. “Thank you,” he replied softly. He held the mug close.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the TV mounted high behind the ferret blinked, the coyote’s eyes quickly snapped to it, drawn by the change, realizing it was a weather screen. The gaze caught the ferret’s attention as well, who turned to look up at the forecast, and back to Cody with a grim expression. “Looks like we’re both gonna be stuck here for a while… listen, uh,” the ferret turned back to the coyote, pausing a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote chuckled. “Cody...my name’s Cody.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smiling, the ferret nodded. “Thomas. Listen, Cody, if uh...your...friends...don’t arrive for you soon…” he started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s expression fell slightly, his ears leaning back. “It’s that obvious?” The tone, the phrasing and pauses, all told a story that the ferret knew the reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas’ expression fell as well. “Only to someone like me. But, uh,” he quieted his voice to just over a whisper, for only the canine’s ears. “If a room doesn’t clear up, and you don’t find someone to hitch a ride with, within the next 3 hours, I’ll meet you by the employee door down the shower hall. My employee bunk’s big enough for both of us short skinny guys.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody paused a moment after listening. “Tom…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret put a finger to the coyote’s muzzle, hushing him gently, before speaking again with a lowered voice. “You’re cute, and I’ve seen you here twice before in the past couple months, and based on who you left with and showed up with, I can tell what happened, and I don’t want you hurt or worse,” he whispered, before grinning up at the coyote more goofily. “And it’s ‘Thomas’, not ‘Tom’… gay guys don’t go by short names.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote burst out in an intense laugh, far stronger than he expected to at the response and struggling not to spill his gifted coffee. “Ahaha, I...thank you, Thomas, I...I needed that. And...thank you,” he replied as he calmed back down, a softer expression having replaced the more forlorn one he wore before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas smiled, turning to head back towards the counter. “Don’t thank me yet, it’s only for a night, and I don’t put out,” he replied as he padded towards the register he’d been working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody turned back to face the window and the storm, as he leaned onto his knees, the warm aroma of the coffee drifting to his nose. “After what brought me here...me neither,” he whispered to the concoction, whilst staring into the swirling snowscape outside as if it held answers he was desperate to divine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a lot cleaner than the normal bunks,” Cody murmured as the door closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret quietly giggled, reaching over to click on a switch, illuminating a rope light tethered to the wall in an organic squiggle. “Well yeah, each employee gets their own little room like this. Now don’t be too loud, there’s nothing saying I can’t do this, but I don’t want to test things,” he said, reaching behind the coyote to lock the door to the ferret’s tiny, private bunk room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I would’ve figured they’d have y’all sharing stacked bunks, this is kinda nice,” Cody added, more quietly. Casting his glances around, he found a small nook under the folding desk to drop his backpack, before turning to the ferret, who’d already shimmied out of his company smock and hung it on a peg on the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nah, this place was built before they started doing that at the other locations. Both of our luck,” Thomas replied as he poked the coyote’s middle gently. “I won’t push you to take off any more than you want, don’t worry. The only payment I want is to snuggle up with a cute guy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody chuckled, but smiled warmly at the response. “Well at least someone is into me for more than just sexual favors,” he mused, as he started tugging his thick hoodie and shirt up over his head, his ears flicking as the hems cleared them, his gray, tawny, and brown fur slightly matted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas was down to just boxers by the time the coyote slipped the top garments off, and wore a soft frown. “That bad?” he asked, softly, with a tone of concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After starting to undo his jeans, Cody paused, and then sat on the small bed beside Thomas. “Yeah. I...I should’ve seen it coming. I moved clear across the country for that asshole and he got pissed just cause I wouldn’t fuck his friends or do drugs with them, and told me I was too ‘weird’ with...my..uhm…”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ferret poked at the coyote’s barely-covered waist, trying not to outright grope him. “With making the house smell like latex or balloons?” Thomas asked with a bit of a grin, gently pinching the waistband of the black latex boxer briefs the coyote’d stopped undressing to hide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cody’s cheeks tinged pink for a moment, but he nodded, slipping those jeans off entirely to let the glossy garment shine in the dim light. “Both. You’re uh...you’re good.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas laughed softly, then bent over for a small bag on the floor. After retrieving something, he stripped his boxers off entirely, not making any attempt to hide his cute butt from the coyote, until he stepped into the garment he’d fetched and slid it up. And as he sat back beside Cody, their hips squeaked lightly, the ferret changed into a matching pair of latex shorts, though purple. “Comes with familiarity, I guess. Now get under the covers here; I’ve always wanted to snuggle up wearing these with a guy who also is, and it’s fucking cold, you damn canines have no concept of indoor temps with that warmer coat.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote paused, taken by significant surprise, and blushing a little more as he shifted to the back of the cot to let Thomas slide in in front of him, and drew the blankets up over the pair. He wrapped an arm around Thomas’ side, gentle at first, and then relaxing as he settled into the contact, quietly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few moments of the quiet affection, with hips lightly squeaking with their gentle movements, the ferret turned to face Cody, and pressed his face into that warm, fluffy chest. “Hope we both can find who we’re looking for,” he spoke softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Cause you don’t have room or money to take me in; I wasn’t even thinking of asking, don’t worry,” Cody replied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, you silly dog, because we’re both such bottoms we’d drive each other nuts!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote had to tuck his snout into the pillow to muffle his laughter. Clocked, teased, and it all true. “Fuck, you’re right, snrk… But this?” he asked, emphasizing his intent as he stroked his claws softly through the ferret’s fur along his back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thomas squirmed and wiggled in true noodle fashion with a chitter, followed by a giggle. “This? Cuddling a cutie like you? I’m hoping I get to again some night,” he replied sweetly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The coyote rested a paw on the ferret’s rubbery-coated flank, gently squeezing, clearly more to explore the material than outright grope his new friend. “Me too.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Story/One for the Road"></category><category term="one_for_the_road"></category><category term="story"></category></entry></feed>